let BP_trials = [
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_BP/AAB_AAP_1_0.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'NA', test_part: 'BP_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'BP_test', audio: 'AAB_AAP_1_0', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '0', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_BP/AAB_AAP_1_0.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_BP/AAB_AAP_1_3.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'NA', test_part: 'BP_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'BP_test', audio: 'AAB_AAP_1_3', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '3', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_BP/AAB_AAP_1_3.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_BP/AAB_AAP_1_5.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'NA', test_part: 'BP_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'BP_test', audio: 'AAB_AAP_1_5', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '5', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_BP/AAB_AAP_1_5.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_BP/AAB_AAP_1_7.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'NA', test_part: 'BP_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'BP_test', audio: 'AAB_AAP_1_7', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '7', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_BP/AAB_AAP_1_7.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_BP/AAB_AAP_1_9.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'NA', test_part: 'BP_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'BP_test', audio: 'AAB_AAP_1_9', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '9', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_BP/AAB_AAP_1_9.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_BP/AAB_AAP_1_10.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'NA', test_part: 'BP_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'BP_test', audio: 'AAB_AAP_1_10', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '10', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_BP/AAB_AAP_1_10.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_BP/AAB_AAP_1_11.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'NA', test_part: 'BP_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'BP_test', audio: 'AAB_AAP_1_11', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '11', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_BP/AAB_AAP_1_11.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_BP/AAB_AAP_1_13.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'NA', test_part: 'BP_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'BP_test', audio: 'AAB_AAP_1_13', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '13', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_BP/AAB_AAP_1_13.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_BP/AAB_AAP_1_17.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'NA', test_part: 'BP_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'BP_test', audio: 'AAB_AAP_1_17', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '17', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_BP/AAB_AAP_1_17.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_BP/AAB_AAP_1_23.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'NA', test_part: 'BP_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'BP_test', audio: 'AAB_AAP_1_23', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '23', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_BP/AAB_AAP_1_23.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_BP/AAB_AAP_1_30.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'NA', test_part: 'BP_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'BP_test', audio: 'AAB_AAP_1_30', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '30', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_BP/AAB_AAP_1_30.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_BP/AHB_AHP_3_0.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'NA', test_part: 'BP_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'BP_test', audio: 'AHB_AHP_3_0', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '0', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_BP/AHB_AHP_3_0.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_BP/AHB_AHP_3_3.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'NA', test_part: 'BP_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'BP_test', audio: 'AHB_AHP_3_3', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '3', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_BP/AHB_AHP_3_3.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_BP/AHB_AHP_3_5.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'NA', test_part: 'BP_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'BP_test', audio: 'AHB_AHP_3_5', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '5', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_BP/AHB_AHP_3_5.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_BP/AHB_AHP_3_7.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'NA', test_part: 'BP_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'BP_test', audio: 'AHB_AHP_3_7', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '7', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_BP/AHB_AHP_3_7.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_BP/AHB_AHP_3_9.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'NA', test_part: 'BP_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'BP_test', audio: 'AHB_AHP_3_9', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '9', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_BP/AHB_AHP_3_9.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_BP/AHB_AHP_3_10.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'NA', test_part: 'BP_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'BP_test', audio: 'AHB_AHP_3_10', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '10', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_BP/AHB_AHP_3_10.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_BP/AHB_AHP_3_11.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'NA', test_part: 'BP_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'BP_test', audio: 'AHB_AHP_3_11', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '11', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_BP/AHB_AHP_3_11.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_BP/AHB_AHP_3_13.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'NA', test_part: 'BP_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'BP_test', audio: 'AHB_AHP_3_13', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '13', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_BP/AHB_AHP_3_13.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_BP/AHB_AHP_3_17.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'NA', test_part: 'BP_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'BP_test', audio: 'AHB_AHP_3_17', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '17', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_BP/AHB_AHP_3_17.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_BP/AHB_AHP_3_23.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'NA', test_part: 'BP_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'BP_test', audio: 'AHB_AHP_3_23', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '23', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_BP/AHB_AHP_3_23.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_BP/AHB_AHP_3_30.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'NA', test_part: 'BP_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'BP_test', audio: 'AHB_AHP_3_30', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '30', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_BP/AHB_AHP_3_30.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_BP/IHB_IHP_5_0.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'NA', test_part: 'BP_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'BP_test', audio: 'IHB_IHP_5_0', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '7', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '0', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_BP/IHB_IHP_5_0.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_BP/IHB_IHP_5_2.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'NA', test_part: 'BP_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'BP_test', audio: 'IHB_IHP_5_2', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '7', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '2', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_BP/IHB_IHP_5_2.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_BP/IHB_IHP_5_4.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'NA', test_part: 'BP_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'BP_test', audio: 'IHB_IHP_5_4', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '7', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '4', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_BP/IHB_IHP_5_4.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_BP/IHB_IHP_5_5.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'NA', test_part: 'BP_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'BP_test', audio: 'IHB_IHP_5_5', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '7', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '5', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_BP/IHB_IHP_5_5.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_BP/IHB_IHP_5_6.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'NA', test_part: 'BP_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'BP_test', audio: 'IHB_IHP_5_6', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '7', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '6', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_BP/IHB_IHP_5_6.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_BP/IHB_IHP_5_7.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'NA', test_part: 'BP_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'BP_test', audio: 'IHB_IHP_5_7', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '7', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '7', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_BP/IHB_IHP_5_7.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_BP/IHB_IHP_5_9.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'NA', test_part: 'BP_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'BP_test', audio: 'IHB_IHP_5_9', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '7', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '9', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_BP/IHB_IHP_5_9.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_BP/IHB_IHP_5_11.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'NA', test_part: 'BP_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'BP_test', audio: 'IHB_IHP_5_11', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '7', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '11', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_BP/IHB_IHP_5_11.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_BP/IHB_IHP_5_15.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'NA', test_part: 'BP_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'BP_test', audio: 'IHB_IHP_5_15', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '7', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '15', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_BP/IHB_IHP_5_15.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_BP/IHB_IHP_5_22.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'NA', test_part: 'BP_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'BP_test', audio: 'IHB_IHP_5_22', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '7', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '22', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_BP/IHB_IHP_5_22.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_BP/IHB_IHP_5_30.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'NA', test_part: 'BP_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'BP_test', audio: 'IHB_IHP_5_30', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '7', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '30', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_BP/IHB_IHP_5_30.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_BP/UHB_UHP_5_0.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'NA', test_part: 'BP_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'BP_test', audio: 'UHB_UHP_5_0', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '7', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '0', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_BP/UHB_UHP_5_0.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_BP/UHB_UHP_5_2.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'NA', test_part: 'BP_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'BP_test', audio: 'UHB_UHP_5_2', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '7', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '2', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_BP/UHB_UHP_5_2.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_BP/UHB_UHP_5_4.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'NA', test_part: 'BP_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'BP_test', audio: 'UHB_UHP_5_4', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '7', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '4', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_BP/UHB_UHP_5_4.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_BP/UHB_UHP_5_5.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'NA', test_part: 'BP_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'BP_test', audio: 'UHB_UHP_5_5', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '7', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '5', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_BP/UHB_UHP_5_5.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_BP/UHB_UHP_5_6.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'NA', test_part: 'BP_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'BP_test', audio: 'UHB_UHP_5_6', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '7', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '6', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_BP/UHB_UHP_5_6.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_BP/UHB_UHP_5_7.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'NA', test_part: 'BP_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'BP_test', audio: 'UHB_UHP_5_7', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '7', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '7', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_BP/UHB_UHP_5_7.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_BP/UHB_UHP_5_9.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'NA', test_part: 'BP_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'BP_test', audio: 'UHB_UHP_5_9', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '7', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '9', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_BP/UHB_UHP_5_9.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_BP/UHB_UHP_5_11.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'NA', test_part: 'BP_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'BP_test', audio: 'UHB_UHP_5_11', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '7', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '11', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_BP/UHB_UHP_5_11.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_BP/UHB_UHP_5_15.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'NA', test_part: 'BP_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'BP_test', audio: 'UHB_UHP_5_15', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '7', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '15', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_BP/UHB_UHP_5_15.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_BP/UHB_UHP_5_21.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'NA', test_part: 'BP_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'BP_test', audio: 'UHB_UHP_5_21', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '7', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '21', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_BP/UHB_UHP_5_21.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_BP/UHB_UHP_5_30.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'NA', test_part: 'BP_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'BP_test', audio: 'UHB_UHP_5_30', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '7', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '30', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_BP/UHB_UHP_5_30.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_BP/AAB_AAP_1_0.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'NA', test_part: 'BP_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'BP_test', audio: 'AAB_AAP_1_0', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '0', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_BP/AAB_AAP_1_0.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_BP/AAB_AAP_1_3.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'NA', test_part: 'BP_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'BP_test', audio: 'AAB_AAP_1_3', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '3', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_BP/AAB_AAP_1_3.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_BP/AAB_AAP_1_5.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'NA', test_part: 'BP_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'BP_test', audio: 'AAB_AAP_1_5', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '5', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_BP/AAB_AAP_1_5.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_BP/AAB_AAP_1_7.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'NA', test_part: 'BP_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'BP_test', audio: 'AAB_AAP_1_7', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '7', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_BP/AAB_AAP_1_7.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_BP/AAB_AAP_1_9.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'NA', test_part: 'BP_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'BP_test', audio: 'AAB_AAP_1_9', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '9', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_BP/AAB_AAP_1_9.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_BP/AAB_AAP_1_10.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'NA', test_part: 'BP_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'BP_test', audio: 'AAB_AAP_1_10', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '10', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_BP/AAB_AAP_1_10.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_BP/AAB_AAP_1_11.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'NA', test_part: 'BP_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'BP_test', audio: 'AAB_AAP_1_11', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '11', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_BP/AAB_AAP_1_11.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_BP/AAB_AAP_1_13.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'NA', test_part: 'BP_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'BP_test', audio: 'AAB_AAP_1_13', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '13', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_BP/AAB_AAP_1_13.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_BP/AAB_AAP_1_17.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'NA', test_part: 'BP_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'BP_test', audio: 'AAB_AAP_1_17', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '17', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_BP/AAB_AAP_1_17.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_BP/AAB_AAP_1_23.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'NA', test_part: 'BP_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'BP_test', audio: 'AAB_AAP_1_23', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '23', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_BP/AAB_AAP_1_23.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_BP/AAB_AAP_1_30.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'NA', test_part: 'BP_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'BP_test', audio: 'AAB_AAP_1_30', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '30', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_BP/AAB_AAP_1_30.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_BP/AHB_AHP_3_0.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'NA', test_part: 'BP_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'BP_test', audio: 'AHB_AHP_3_0', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '0', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_BP/AHB_AHP_3_0.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_BP/AHB_AHP_3_3.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'NA', test_part: 'BP_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'BP_test', audio: 'AHB_AHP_3_3', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '3', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_BP/AHB_AHP_3_3.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_BP/AHB_AHP_3_5.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'NA', test_part: 'BP_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'BP_test', audio: 'AHB_AHP_3_5', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '5', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_BP/AHB_AHP_3_5.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_BP/AHB_AHP_3_7.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'NA', test_part: 'BP_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'BP_test', audio: 'AHB_AHP_3_7', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '7', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_BP/AHB_AHP_3_7.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_BP/AHB_AHP_3_9.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'NA', test_part: 'BP_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'BP_test', audio: 'AHB_AHP_3_9', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '9', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_BP/AHB_AHP_3_9.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_BP/AHB_AHP_3_10.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'NA', test_part: 'BP_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'BP_test', audio: 'AHB_AHP_3_10', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '10', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_BP/AHB_AHP_3_10.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_BP/AHB_AHP_3_11.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'NA', test_part: 'BP_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'BP_test', audio: 'AHB_AHP_3_11', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '11', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_BP/AHB_AHP_3_11.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_BP/AHB_AHP_3_13.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'NA', test_part: 'BP_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'BP_test', audio: 'AHB_AHP_3_13', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '13', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_BP/AHB_AHP_3_13.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_BP/AHB_AHP_3_17.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'NA', test_part: 'BP_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'BP_test', audio: 'AHB_AHP_3_17', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '17', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_BP/AHB_AHP_3_17.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_BP/AHB_AHP_3_23.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'NA', test_part: 'BP_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'BP_test', audio: 'AHB_AHP_3_23', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '23', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_BP/AHB_AHP_3_23.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_BP/AHB_AHP_3_30.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'NA', test_part: 'BP_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'BP_test', audio: 'AHB_AHP_3_30', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '30', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_BP/AHB_AHP_3_30.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_BP/IHB_IHP_5_0.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'NA', test_part: 'BP_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'BP_test', audio: 'IHB_IHP_5_0', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '7', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '0', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_BP/IHB_IHP_5_0.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_BP/IHB_IHP_5_2.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'NA', test_part: 'BP_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'BP_test', audio: 'IHB_IHP_5_2', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '7', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '2', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_BP/IHB_IHP_5_2.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_BP/IHB_IHP_5_4.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'NA', test_part: 'BP_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'BP_test', audio: 'IHB_IHP_5_4', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '7', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '4', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_BP/IHB_IHP_5_4.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_BP/IHB_IHP_5_5.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'NA', test_part: 'BP_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'BP_test', audio: 'IHB_IHP_5_5', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '7', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '5', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_BP/IHB_IHP_5_5.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_BP/IHB_IHP_5_6.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'NA', test_part: 'BP_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'BP_test', audio: 'IHB_IHP_5_6', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '7', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '6', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_BP/IHB_IHP_5_6.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_BP/IHB_IHP_5_7.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'NA', test_part: 'BP_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'BP_test', audio: 'IHB_IHP_5_7', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '7', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '7', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_BP/IHB_IHP_5_7.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_BP/IHB_IHP_5_9.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'NA', test_part: 'BP_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'BP_test', audio: 'IHB_IHP_5_9', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '7', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '9', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_BP/IHB_IHP_5_9.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_BP/IHB_IHP_5_11.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'NA', test_part: 'BP_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'BP_test', audio: 'IHB_IHP_5_11', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '7', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '11', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_BP/IHB_IHP_5_11.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_BP/IHB_IHP_5_15.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'NA', test_part: 'BP_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'BP_test', audio: 'IHB_IHP_5_15', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '7', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '15', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_BP/IHB_IHP_5_15.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_BP/IHB_IHP_5_22.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'NA', test_part: 'BP_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'BP_test', audio: 'IHB_IHP_5_22', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '7', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '22', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_BP/IHB_IHP_5_22.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_BP/IHB_IHP_5_30.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'NA', test_part: 'BP_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'BP_test', audio: 'IHB_IHP_5_30', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '7', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '30', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_BP/IHB_IHP_5_30.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_BP/UHB_UHP_5_0.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'NA', test_part: 'BP_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'BP_test', audio: 'UHB_UHP_5_0', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '7', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '0', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_BP/UHB_UHP_5_0.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_BP/UHB_UHP_5_2.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'NA', test_part: 'BP_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'BP_test', audio: 'UHB_UHP_5_2', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '7', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '2', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_BP/UHB_UHP_5_2.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_BP/UHB_UHP_5_4.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'NA', test_part: 'BP_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'BP_test', audio: 'UHB_UHP_5_4', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '7', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '4', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_BP/UHB_UHP_5_4.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_BP/UHB_UHP_5_5.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'NA', test_part: 'BP_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'BP_test', audio: 'UHB_UHP_5_5', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '7', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '5', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_BP/UHB_UHP_5_5.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_BP/UHB_UHP_5_6.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'NA', test_part: 'BP_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'BP_test', audio: 'UHB_UHP_5_6', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '7', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '6', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_BP/UHB_UHP_5_6.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_BP/UHB_UHP_5_7.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'NA', test_part: 'BP_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'BP_test', audio: 'UHB_UHP_5_7', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '7', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '7', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_BP/UHB_UHP_5_7.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_BP/UHB_UHP_5_9.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'NA', test_part: 'BP_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'BP_test', audio: 'UHB_UHP_5_9', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '7', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '9', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_BP/UHB_UHP_5_9.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_BP/UHB_UHP_5_11.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'NA', test_part: 'BP_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'BP_test', audio: 'UHB_UHP_5_11', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '7', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '11', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_BP/UHB_UHP_5_11.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_BP/UHB_UHP_5_15.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'NA', test_part: 'BP_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'BP_test', audio: 'UHB_UHP_5_15', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '7', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '15', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_BP/UHB_UHP_5_15.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_BP/UHB_UHP_5_21.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'NA', test_part: 'BP_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'BP_test', audio: 'UHB_UHP_5_21', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '7', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '21', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_BP/UHB_UHP_5_21.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_BP/UHB_UHP_5_30.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'NA', test_part: 'BP_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'BP_test', audio: 'UHB_UHP_5_30', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '7', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '30', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_BP/UHB_UHP_5_30.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_BP/AAB_AAP_1_0.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'NA', test_part: 'BP_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'BP_test', audio: 'AAB_AAP_1_0', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '0', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_BP/AAB_AAP_1_0.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_BP/AAB_AAP_1_3.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'NA', test_part: 'BP_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'BP_test', audio: 'AAB_AAP_1_3', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '3', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_BP/AAB_AAP_1_3.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_BP/AAB_AAP_1_5.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'NA', test_part: 'BP_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'BP_test', audio: 'AAB_AAP_1_5', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '5', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_BP/AAB_AAP_1_5.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_BP/AAB_AAP_1_7.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'NA', test_part: 'BP_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'BP_test', audio: 'AAB_AAP_1_7', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '7', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_BP/AAB_AAP_1_7.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_BP/AAB_AAP_1_9.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'NA', test_part: 'BP_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'BP_test', audio: 'AAB_AAP_1_9', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '9', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_BP/AAB_AAP_1_9.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_BP/AAB_AAP_1_10.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'NA', test_part: 'BP_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'BP_test', audio: 'AAB_AAP_1_10', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '10', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_BP/AAB_AAP_1_10.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_BP/AAB_AAP_1_11.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'NA', test_part: 'BP_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'BP_test', audio: 'AAB_AAP_1_11', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '11', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_BP/AAB_AAP_1_11.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_BP/AAB_AAP_1_13.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'NA', test_part: 'BP_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'BP_test', audio: 'AAB_AAP_1_13', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '13', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_BP/AAB_AAP_1_13.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_BP/AAB_AAP_1_17.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'NA', test_part: 'BP_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'BP_test', audio: 'AAB_AAP_1_17', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '17', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_BP/AAB_AAP_1_17.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_BP/AAB_AAP_1_23.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'NA', test_part: 'BP_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'BP_test', audio: 'AAB_AAP_1_23', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '23', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_BP/AAB_AAP_1_23.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_BP/AAB_AAP_1_30.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'NA', test_part: 'BP_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'BP_test', audio: 'AAB_AAP_1_30', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '30', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_BP/AAB_AAP_1_30.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_BP/AHB_AHP_3_0.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'NA', test_part: 'BP_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'BP_test', audio: 'AHB_AHP_3_0', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '0', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_BP/AHB_AHP_3_0.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_BP/AHB_AHP_3_3.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'NA', test_part: 'BP_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'BP_test', audio: 'AHB_AHP_3_3', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '3', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_BP/AHB_AHP_3_3.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_BP/AHB_AHP_3_5.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'NA', test_part: 'BP_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'BP_test', audio: 'AHB_AHP_3_5', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '5', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_BP/AHB_AHP_3_5.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_BP/AHB_AHP_3_7.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'NA', test_part: 'BP_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'BP_test', audio: 'AHB_AHP_3_7', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '7', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_BP/AHB_AHP_3_7.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_BP/AHB_AHP_3_9.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'NA', test_part: 'BP_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'BP_test', audio: 'AHB_AHP_3_9', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '9', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_BP/AHB_AHP_3_9.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_BP/AHB_AHP_3_10.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'NA', test_part: 'BP_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'BP_test', audio: 'AHB_AHP_3_10', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '10', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_BP/AHB_AHP_3_10.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_BP/AHB_AHP_3_11.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'NA', test_part: 'BP_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'BP_test', audio: 'AHB_AHP_3_11', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '11', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_BP/AHB_AHP_3_11.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_BP/AHB_AHP_3_13.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'NA', test_part: 'BP_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'BP_test', audio: 'AHB_AHP_3_13', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '13', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_BP/AHB_AHP_3_13.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_BP/AHB_AHP_3_17.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'NA', test_part: 'BP_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'BP_test', audio: 'AHB_AHP_3_17', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '17', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_BP/AHB_AHP_3_17.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_BP/AHB_AHP_3_23.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'NA', test_part: 'BP_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'BP_test', audio: 'AHB_AHP_3_23', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '23', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_BP/AHB_AHP_3_23.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_BP/AHB_AHP_3_30.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'NA', test_part: 'BP_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'BP_test', audio: 'AHB_AHP_3_30', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '30', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_BP/AHB_AHP_3_30.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_BP/IHB_IHP_5_0.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'NA', test_part: 'BP_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'BP_test', audio: 'IHB_IHP_5_0', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '7', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '0', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_BP/IHB_IHP_5_0.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_BP/IHB_IHP_5_2.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'NA', test_part: 'BP_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'BP_test', audio: 'IHB_IHP_5_2', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '7', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '2', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_BP/IHB_IHP_5_2.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_BP/IHB_IHP_5_4.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'NA', test_part: 'BP_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'BP_test', audio: 'IHB_IHP_5_4', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '7', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '4', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_BP/IHB_IHP_5_4.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_BP/IHB_IHP_5_5.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'NA', test_part: 'BP_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'BP_test', audio: 'IHB_IHP_5_5', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '7', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '5', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_BP/IHB_IHP_5_5.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_BP/IHB_IHP_5_6.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'NA', test_part: 'BP_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'BP_test', audio: 'IHB_IHP_5_6', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '7', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '6', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_BP/IHB_IHP_5_6.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_BP/IHB_IHP_5_7.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'NA', test_part: 'BP_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'BP_test', audio: 'IHB_IHP_5_7', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '7', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '7', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_BP/IHB_IHP_5_7.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_BP/IHB_IHP_5_9.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'NA', test_part: 'BP_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'BP_test', audio: 'IHB_IHP_5_9', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '7', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '9', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_BP/IHB_IHP_5_9.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_BP/IHB_IHP_5_11.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'NA', test_part: 'BP_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'BP_test', audio: 'IHB_IHP_5_11', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '7', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '11', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_BP/IHB_IHP_5_11.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_BP/IHB_IHP_5_15.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'NA', test_part: 'BP_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'BP_test', audio: 'IHB_IHP_5_15', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '7', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '15', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_BP/IHB_IHP_5_15.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_BP/IHB_IHP_5_22.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'NA', test_part: 'BP_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'BP_test', audio: 'IHB_IHP_5_22', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '7', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '22', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_BP/IHB_IHP_5_22.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_BP/IHB_IHP_5_30.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'NA', test_part: 'BP_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'BP_test', audio: 'IHB_IHP_5_30', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '7', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '30', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_BP/IHB_IHP_5_30.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_BP/UHB_UHP_5_0.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'NA', test_part: 'BP_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'BP_test', audio: 'UHB_UHP_5_0', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '7', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '0', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_BP/UHB_UHP_5_0.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_BP/UHB_UHP_5_2.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'NA', test_part: 'BP_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'BP_test', audio: 'UHB_UHP_5_2', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '7', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '2', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_BP/UHB_UHP_5_2.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_BP/UHB_UHP_5_4.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'NA', test_part: 'BP_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'BP_test', audio: 'UHB_UHP_5_4', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '7', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '4', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_BP/UHB_UHP_5_4.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_BP/UHB_UHP_5_5.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'NA', test_part: 'BP_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'BP_test', audio: 'UHB_UHP_5_5', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '7', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '5', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_BP/UHB_UHP_5_5.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_BP/UHB_UHP_5_6.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'NA', test_part: 'BP_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'BP_test', audio: 'UHB_UHP_5_6', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '7', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '6', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_BP/UHB_UHP_5_6.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_BP/UHB_UHP_5_7.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'NA', test_part: 'BP_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'BP_test', audio: 'UHB_UHP_5_7', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '7', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '7', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_BP/UHB_UHP_5_7.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_BP/UHB_UHP_5_9.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'NA', test_part: 'BP_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'BP_test', audio: 'UHB_UHP_5_9', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '7', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '9', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_BP/UHB_UHP_5_9.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_BP/UHB_UHP_5_11.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'NA', test_part: 'BP_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'BP_test', audio: 'UHB_UHP_5_11', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '7', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '11', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_BP/UHB_UHP_5_11.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_BP/UHB_UHP_5_15.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'NA', test_part: 'BP_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'BP_test', audio: 'UHB_UHP_5_15', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '7', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '15', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_BP/UHB_UHP_5_15.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_BP/UHB_UHP_5_21.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'NA', test_part: 'BP_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'BP_test', audio: 'UHB_UHP_5_21', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '7', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '21', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_BP/UHB_UHP_5_21.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_BP/UHB_UHP_5_30.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'NA', test_part: 'BP_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'BP_test', audio: 'UHB_UHP_5_30', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '7', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '30', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_BP/UHB_UHP_5_30.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_BP/AAB_AAP_1_0.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'NA', test_part: 'BP_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'BP_test', audio: 'AAB_AAP_1_0', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '0', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_BP/AAB_AAP_1_0.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_BP/AAB_AAP_1_3.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'NA', test_part: 'BP_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'BP_test', audio: 'AAB_AAP_1_3', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '3', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_BP/AAB_AAP_1_3.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_BP/AAB_AAP_1_5.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'NA', test_part: 'BP_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'BP_test', audio: 'AAB_AAP_1_5', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '5', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_BP/AAB_AAP_1_5.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_BP/AAB_AAP_1_7.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'NA', test_part: 'BP_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'BP_test', audio: 'AAB_AAP_1_7', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '7', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_BP/AAB_AAP_1_7.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_BP/AAB_AAP_1_9.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'NA', test_part: 'BP_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'BP_test', audio: 'AAB_AAP_1_9', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '9', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_BP/AAB_AAP_1_9.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_BP/AAB_AAP_1_10.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'NA', test_part: 'BP_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'BP_test', audio: 'AAB_AAP_1_10', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '10', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_BP/AAB_AAP_1_10.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_BP/AAB_AAP_1_11.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'NA', test_part: 'BP_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'BP_test', audio: 'AAB_AAP_1_11', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '11', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_BP/AAB_AAP_1_11.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_BP/AAB_AAP_1_13.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'NA', test_part: 'BP_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'BP_test', audio: 'AAB_AAP_1_13', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '13', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_BP/AAB_AAP_1_13.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_BP/AAB_AAP_1_17.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'NA', test_part: 'BP_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'BP_test', audio: 'AAB_AAP_1_17', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '17', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_BP/AAB_AAP_1_17.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_BP/AAB_AAP_1_23.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'NA', test_part: 'BP_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'BP_test', audio: 'AAB_AAP_1_23', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '23', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_BP/AAB_AAP_1_23.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_BP/AAB_AAP_1_30.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'NA', test_part: 'BP_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'BP_test', audio: 'AAB_AAP_1_30', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '30', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_BP/AAB_AAP_1_30.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_BP/AHB_AHP_3_0.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'NA', test_part: 'BP_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'BP_test', audio: 'AHB_AHP_3_0', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '0', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_BP/AHB_AHP_3_0.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_BP/AHB_AHP_3_3.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'NA', test_part: 'BP_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'BP_test', audio: 'AHB_AHP_3_3', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '3', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_BP/AHB_AHP_3_3.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_BP/AHB_AHP_3_5.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'NA', test_part: 'BP_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'BP_test', audio: 'AHB_AHP_3_5', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '5', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_BP/AHB_AHP_3_5.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_BP/AHB_AHP_3_7.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'NA', test_part: 'BP_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'BP_test', audio: 'AHB_AHP_3_7', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '7', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_BP/AHB_AHP_3_7.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_BP/AHB_AHP_3_9.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'NA', test_part: 'BP_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'BP_test', audio: 'AHB_AHP_3_9', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '9', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_BP/AHB_AHP_3_9.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_BP/AHB_AHP_3_10.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'NA', test_part: 'BP_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'BP_test', audio: 'AHB_AHP_3_10', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '10', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_BP/AHB_AHP_3_10.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_BP/AHB_AHP_3_11.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'NA', test_part: 'BP_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'BP_test', audio: 'AHB_AHP_3_11', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '11', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_BP/AHB_AHP_3_11.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_BP/AHB_AHP_3_13.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'NA', test_part: 'BP_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'BP_test', audio: 'AHB_AHP_3_13', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '13', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_BP/AHB_AHP_3_13.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_BP/AHB_AHP_3_17.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'NA', test_part: 'BP_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'BP_test', audio: 'AHB_AHP_3_17', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '17', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_BP/AHB_AHP_3_17.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_BP/AHB_AHP_3_23.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'NA', test_part: 'BP_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'BP_test', audio: 'AHB_AHP_3_23', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '23', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_BP/AHB_AHP_3_23.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_BP/AHB_AHP_3_30.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'NA', test_part: 'BP_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'BP_test', audio: 'AHB_AHP_3_30', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '30', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_BP/AHB_AHP_3_30.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_BP/IHB_IHP_5_0.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'NA', test_part: 'BP_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'BP_test', audio: 'IHB_IHP_5_0', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '7', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '0', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_BP/IHB_IHP_5_0.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_BP/IHB_IHP_5_2.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'NA', test_part: 'BP_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'BP_test', audio: 'IHB_IHP_5_2', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '7', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '2', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_BP/IHB_IHP_5_2.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_BP/IHB_IHP_5_4.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'NA', test_part: 'BP_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'BP_test', audio: 'IHB_IHP_5_4', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '7', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '4', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_BP/IHB_IHP_5_4.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_BP/IHB_IHP_5_5.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'NA', test_part: 'BP_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'BP_test', audio: 'IHB_IHP_5_5', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '7', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '5', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_BP/IHB_IHP_5_5.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_BP/IHB_IHP_5_6.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'NA', test_part: 'BP_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'BP_test', audio: 'IHB_IHP_5_6', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '7', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '6', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_BP/IHB_IHP_5_6.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_BP/IHB_IHP_5_7.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'NA', test_part: 'BP_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'BP_test', audio: 'IHB_IHP_5_7', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '7', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '7', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_BP/IHB_IHP_5_7.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_BP/IHB_IHP_5_9.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'NA', test_part: 'BP_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'BP_test', audio: 'IHB_IHP_5_9', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '7', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '9', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_BP/IHB_IHP_5_9.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_BP/IHB_IHP_5_11.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'NA', test_part: 'BP_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'BP_test', audio: 'IHB_IHP_5_11', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '7', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '11', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_BP/IHB_IHP_5_11.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_BP/IHB_IHP_5_15.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'NA', test_part: 'BP_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'BP_test', audio: 'IHB_IHP_5_15', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '7', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '15', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_BP/IHB_IHP_5_15.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_BP/IHB_IHP_5_22.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'NA', test_part: 'BP_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'BP_test', audio: 'IHB_IHP_5_22', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '7', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '22', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_BP/IHB_IHP_5_22.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_BP/IHB_IHP_5_30.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'NA', test_part: 'BP_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'BP_test', audio: 'IHB_IHP_5_30', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '7', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '30', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_BP/IHB_IHP_5_30.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_BP/UHB_UHP_5_0.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'NA', test_part: 'BP_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'BP_test', audio: 'UHB_UHP_5_0', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '7', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '0', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_BP/UHB_UHP_5_0.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_BP/UHB_UHP_5_2.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'NA', test_part: 'BP_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'BP_test', audio: 'UHB_UHP_5_2', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '7', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '2', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_BP/UHB_UHP_5_2.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_BP/UHB_UHP_5_4.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'NA', test_part: 'BP_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'BP_test', audio: 'UHB_UHP_5_4', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '7', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '4', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_BP/UHB_UHP_5_4.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_BP/UHB_UHP_5_5.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'NA', test_part: 'BP_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'BP_test', audio: 'UHB_UHP_5_5', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '7', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '5', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_BP/UHB_UHP_5_5.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_BP/UHB_UHP_5_6.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'NA', test_part: 'BP_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'BP_test', audio: 'UHB_UHP_5_6', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '7', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '6', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_BP/UHB_UHP_5_6.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_BP/UHB_UHP_5_7.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'NA', test_part: 'BP_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'BP_test', audio: 'UHB_UHP_5_7', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '7', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '7', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_BP/UHB_UHP_5_7.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_BP/UHB_UHP_5_9.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'NA', test_part: 'BP_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'BP_test', audio: 'UHB_UHP_5_9', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '7', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '9', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_BP/UHB_UHP_5_9.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_BP/UHB_UHP_5_11.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'NA', test_part: 'BP_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'BP_test', audio: 'UHB_UHP_5_11', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '7', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '11', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_BP/UHB_UHP_5_11.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_BP/UHB_UHP_5_15.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'NA', test_part: 'BP_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'BP_test', audio: 'UHB_UHP_5_15', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '7', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '15', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_BP/UHB_UHP_5_15.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_BP/UHB_UHP_5_21.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'NA', test_part: 'BP_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'BP_test', audio: 'UHB_UHP_5_21', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '7', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '21', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_BP/UHB_UHP_5_21.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_BP/UHB_UHP_5_30.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'NA', test_part: 'BP_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'BP_test', audio: 'UHB_UHP_5_30', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '7', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '30', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_BP/UHB_UHP_5_30.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_BP/AAB_AAP_1_0.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'NA', test_part: 'BP_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'BP_test', audio: 'AAB_AAP_1_0', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '0', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_BP/AAB_AAP_1_0.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_BP/AAB_AAP_1_3.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'NA', test_part: 'BP_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'BP_test', audio: 'AAB_AAP_1_3', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '3', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_BP/AAB_AAP_1_3.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_BP/AAB_AAP_1_5.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'NA', test_part: 'BP_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'BP_test', audio: 'AAB_AAP_1_5', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '5', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_BP/AAB_AAP_1_5.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_BP/AAB_AAP_1_7.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'NA', test_part: 'BP_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'BP_test', audio: 'AAB_AAP_1_7', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '7', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_BP/AAB_AAP_1_7.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_BP/AAB_AAP_1_9.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'NA', test_part: 'BP_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'BP_test', audio: 'AAB_AAP_1_9', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '9', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_BP/AAB_AAP_1_9.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_BP/AAB_AAP_1_10.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'NA', test_part: 'BP_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'BP_test', audio: 'AAB_AAP_1_10', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '10', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_BP/AAB_AAP_1_10.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_BP/AAB_AAP_1_11.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'NA', test_part: 'BP_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'BP_test', audio: 'AAB_AAP_1_11', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '11', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_BP/AAB_AAP_1_11.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_BP/AAB_AAP_1_13.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'NA', test_part: 'BP_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'BP_test', audio: 'AAB_AAP_1_13', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '13', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_BP/AAB_AAP_1_13.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_BP/AAB_AAP_1_17.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'NA', test_part: 'BP_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'BP_test', audio: 'AAB_AAP_1_17', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '17', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_BP/AAB_AAP_1_17.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_BP/AAB_AAP_1_23.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'NA', test_part: 'BP_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'BP_test', audio: 'AAB_AAP_1_23', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '23', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_BP/AAB_AAP_1_23.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_BP/AAB_AAP_1_30.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'NA', test_part: 'BP_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'BP_test', audio: 'AAB_AAP_1_30', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '30', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_BP/AAB_AAP_1_30.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_BP/AHB_AHP_3_0.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'NA', test_part: 'BP_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'BP_test', audio: 'AHB_AHP_3_0', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '0', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_BP/AHB_AHP_3_0.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_BP/AHB_AHP_3_3.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'NA', test_part: 'BP_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'BP_test', audio: 'AHB_AHP_3_3', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '3', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_BP/AHB_AHP_3_3.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_BP/AHB_AHP_3_5.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'NA', test_part: 'BP_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'BP_test', audio: 'AHB_AHP_3_5', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '5', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_BP/AHB_AHP_3_5.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_BP/AHB_AHP_3_7.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'NA', test_part: 'BP_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'BP_test', audio: 'AHB_AHP_3_7', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '7', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_BP/AHB_AHP_3_7.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_BP/AHB_AHP_3_9.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'NA', test_part: 'BP_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'BP_test', audio: 'AHB_AHP_3_9', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '9', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_BP/AHB_AHP_3_9.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_BP/AHB_AHP_3_10.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'NA', test_part: 'BP_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'BP_test', audio: 'AHB_AHP_3_10', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '10', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_BP/AHB_AHP_3_10.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_BP/AHB_AHP_3_11.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'NA', test_part: 'BP_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'BP_test', audio: 'AHB_AHP_3_11', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '11', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_BP/AHB_AHP_3_11.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_BP/AHB_AHP_3_13.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'NA', test_part: 'BP_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'BP_test', audio: 'AHB_AHP_3_13', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '13', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_BP/AHB_AHP_3_13.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_BP/AHB_AHP_3_17.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'NA', test_part: 'BP_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'BP_test', audio: 'AHB_AHP_3_17', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '17', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_BP/AHB_AHP_3_17.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_BP/AHB_AHP_3_23.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'NA', test_part: 'BP_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'BP_test', audio: 'AHB_AHP_3_23', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '23', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_BP/AHB_AHP_3_23.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_BP/AHB_AHP_3_30.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'NA', test_part: 'BP_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'BP_test', audio: 'AHB_AHP_3_30', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '30', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_BP/AHB_AHP_3_30.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_BP/IHB_IHP_5_0.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'NA', test_part: 'BP_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'BP_test', audio: 'IHB_IHP_5_0', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '7', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '0', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_BP/IHB_IHP_5_0.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_BP/IHB_IHP_5_2.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'NA', test_part: 'BP_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'BP_test', audio: 'IHB_IHP_5_2', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '7', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '2', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_BP/IHB_IHP_5_2.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_BP/IHB_IHP_5_4.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'NA', test_part: 'BP_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'BP_test', audio: 'IHB_IHP_5_4', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '7', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '4', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_BP/IHB_IHP_5_4.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_BP/IHB_IHP_5_5.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'NA', test_part: 'BP_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'BP_test', audio: 'IHB_IHP_5_5', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '7', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '5', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_BP/IHB_IHP_5_5.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_BP/IHB_IHP_5_6.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'NA', test_part: 'BP_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'BP_test', audio: 'IHB_IHP_5_6', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '7', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '6', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_BP/IHB_IHP_5_6.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_BP/IHB_IHP_5_7.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'NA', test_part: 'BP_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'BP_test', audio: 'IHB_IHP_5_7', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '7', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '7', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_BP/IHB_IHP_5_7.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_BP/IHB_IHP_5_9.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'NA', test_part: 'BP_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'BP_test', audio: 'IHB_IHP_5_9', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '7', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '9', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_BP/IHB_IHP_5_9.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_BP/IHB_IHP_5_11.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'NA', test_part: 'BP_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'BP_test', audio: 'IHB_IHP_5_11', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '7', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '11', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_BP/IHB_IHP_5_11.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_BP/IHB_IHP_5_15.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'NA', test_part: 'BP_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'BP_test', audio: 'IHB_IHP_5_15', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '7', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '15', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_BP/IHB_IHP_5_15.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_BP/IHB_IHP_5_22.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'NA', test_part: 'BP_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'BP_test', audio: 'IHB_IHP_5_22', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '7', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '22', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_BP/IHB_IHP_5_22.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_BP/IHB_IHP_5_30.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'NA', test_part: 'BP_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'BP_test', audio: 'IHB_IHP_5_30', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '7', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '30', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_BP/IHB_IHP_5_30.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_BP/UHB_UHP_5_0.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'NA', test_part: 'BP_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'BP_test', audio: 'UHB_UHP_5_0', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '7', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '0', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_BP/UHB_UHP_5_0.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_BP/UHB_UHP_5_2.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'NA', test_part: 'BP_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'BP_test', audio: 'UHB_UHP_5_2', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '7', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '2', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_BP/UHB_UHP_5_2.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_BP/UHB_UHP_5_4.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'NA', test_part: 'BP_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'BP_test', audio: 'UHB_UHP_5_4', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '7', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '4', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_BP/UHB_UHP_5_4.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_BP/UHB_UHP_5_5.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'NA', test_part: 'BP_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'BP_test', audio: 'UHB_UHP_5_5', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '7', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '5', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_BP/UHB_UHP_5_5.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_BP/UHB_UHP_5_6.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'NA', test_part: 'BP_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'BP_test', audio: 'UHB_UHP_5_6', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '7', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '6', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_BP/UHB_UHP_5_6.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_BP/UHB_UHP_5_7.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'NA', test_part: 'BP_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'BP_test', audio: 'UHB_UHP_5_7', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '7', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '7', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_BP/UHB_UHP_5_7.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_BP/UHB_UHP_5_9.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'NA', test_part: 'BP_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'BP_test', audio: 'UHB_UHP_5_9', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '7', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '9', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_BP/UHB_UHP_5_9.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_BP/UHB_UHP_5_11.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'NA', test_part: 'BP_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'BP_test', audio: 'UHB_UHP_5_11', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '7', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '11', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_BP/UHB_UHP_5_11.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_BP/UHB_UHP_5_15.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'NA', test_part: 'BP_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'BP_test', audio: 'UHB_UHP_5_15', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '7', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '15', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_BP/UHB_UHP_5_15.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_BP/UHB_UHP_5_21.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'NA', test_part: 'BP_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'BP_test', audio: 'UHB_UHP_5_21', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '7', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '21', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_BP/UHB_UHP_5_21.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_BP/UHB_UHP_5_30.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'NA', test_part: 'BP_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'BP_test', audio: 'UHB_UHP_5_30', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '7', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '30', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_BP/UHB_UHP_5_30.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_BP/AAB_AAP_1_0.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'NA', test_part: 'BP_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'BP_test', audio: 'AAB_AAP_1_0', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '0', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_BP/AAB_AAP_1_0.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_BP/AAB_AAP_1_3.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'NA', test_part: 'BP_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'BP_test', audio: 'AAB_AAP_1_3', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '3', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_BP/AAB_AAP_1_3.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_BP/AAB_AAP_1_5.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'NA', test_part: 'BP_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'BP_test', audio: 'AAB_AAP_1_5', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '5', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_BP/AAB_AAP_1_5.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_BP/AAB_AAP_1_7.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'NA', test_part: 'BP_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'BP_test', audio: 'AAB_AAP_1_7', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '7', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_BP/AAB_AAP_1_7.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_BP/AAB_AAP_1_9.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'NA', test_part: 'BP_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'BP_test', audio: 'AAB_AAP_1_9', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '9', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_BP/AAB_AAP_1_9.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_BP/AAB_AAP_1_10.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'NA', test_part: 'BP_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'BP_test', audio: 'AAB_AAP_1_10', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '10', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_BP/AAB_AAP_1_10.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_BP/AAB_AAP_1_11.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'NA', test_part: 'BP_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'BP_test', audio: 'AAB_AAP_1_11', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '11', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_BP/AAB_AAP_1_11.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_BP/AAB_AAP_1_13.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'NA', test_part: 'BP_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'BP_test', audio: 'AAB_AAP_1_13', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '13', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_BP/AAB_AAP_1_13.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_BP/AAB_AAP_1_17.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'NA', test_part: 'BP_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'BP_test', audio: 'AAB_AAP_1_17', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '17', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_BP/AAB_AAP_1_17.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_BP/AAB_AAP_1_23.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'NA', test_part: 'BP_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'BP_test', audio: 'AAB_AAP_1_23', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '23', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_BP/AAB_AAP_1_23.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_BP/AAB_AAP_1_30.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'NA', test_part: 'BP_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'BP_test', audio: 'AAB_AAP_1_30', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '30', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_BP/AAB_AAP_1_30.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_BP/AHB_AHP_3_0.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'NA', test_part: 'BP_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'BP_test', audio: 'AHB_AHP_3_0', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '0', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_BP/AHB_AHP_3_0.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_BP/AHB_AHP_3_3.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'NA', test_part: 'BP_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'BP_test', audio: 'AHB_AHP_3_3', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '3', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_BP/AHB_AHP_3_3.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_BP/AHB_AHP_3_5.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'NA', test_part: 'BP_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'BP_test', audio: 'AHB_AHP_3_5', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '5', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_BP/AHB_AHP_3_5.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_BP/AHB_AHP_3_7.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'NA', test_part: 'BP_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'BP_test', audio: 'AHB_AHP_3_7', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '7', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_BP/AHB_AHP_3_7.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_BP/AHB_AHP_3_9.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'NA', test_part: 'BP_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'BP_test', audio: 'AHB_AHP_3_9', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '9', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_BP/AHB_AHP_3_9.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_BP/AHB_AHP_3_10.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'NA', test_part: 'BP_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'BP_test', audio: 'AHB_AHP_3_10', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '10', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_BP/AHB_AHP_3_10.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_BP/AHB_AHP_3_11.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'NA', test_part: 'BP_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'BP_test', audio: 'AHB_AHP_3_11', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '11', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_BP/AHB_AHP_3_11.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_BP/AHB_AHP_3_13.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'NA', test_part: 'BP_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'BP_test', audio: 'AHB_AHP_3_13', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '13', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_BP/AHB_AHP_3_13.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_BP/AHB_AHP_3_17.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'NA', test_part: 'BP_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'BP_test', audio: 'AHB_AHP_3_17', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '17', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_BP/AHB_AHP_3_17.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_BP/AHB_AHP_3_23.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'NA', test_part: 'BP_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'BP_test', audio: 'AHB_AHP_3_23', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '23', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_BP/AHB_AHP_3_23.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_BP/AHB_AHP_3_30.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'NA', test_part: 'BP_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'BP_test', audio: 'AHB_AHP_3_30', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '30', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_BP/AHB_AHP_3_30.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_BP/IHB_IHP_5_0.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'NA', test_part: 'BP_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'BP_test', audio: 'IHB_IHP_5_0', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '7', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '0', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_BP/IHB_IHP_5_0.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_BP/IHB_IHP_5_2.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'NA', test_part: 'BP_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'BP_test', audio: 'IHB_IHP_5_2', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '7', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '2', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_BP/IHB_IHP_5_2.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_BP/IHB_IHP_5_4.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'NA', test_part: 'BP_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'BP_test', audio: 'IHB_IHP_5_4', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '7', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '4', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_BP/IHB_IHP_5_4.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_BP/IHB_IHP_5_5.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'NA', test_part: 'BP_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'BP_test', audio: 'IHB_IHP_5_5', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '7', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '5', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_BP/IHB_IHP_5_5.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_BP/IHB_IHP_5_6.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'NA', test_part: 'BP_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'BP_test', audio: 'IHB_IHP_5_6', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '7', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '6', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_BP/IHB_IHP_5_6.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_BP/IHB_IHP_5_7.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'NA', test_part: 'BP_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'BP_test', audio: 'IHB_IHP_5_7', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '7', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '7', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_BP/IHB_IHP_5_7.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_BP/IHB_IHP_5_9.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'NA', test_part: 'BP_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'BP_test', audio: 'IHB_IHP_5_9', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '7', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '9', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_BP/IHB_IHP_5_9.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_BP/IHB_IHP_5_11.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'NA', test_part: 'BP_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'BP_test', audio: 'IHB_IHP_5_11', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '7', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '11', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_BP/IHB_IHP_5_11.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_BP/IHB_IHP_5_15.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'NA', test_part: 'BP_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'BP_test', audio: 'IHB_IHP_5_15', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '7', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '15', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_BP/IHB_IHP_5_15.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_BP/IHB_IHP_5_22.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'NA', test_part: 'BP_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'BP_test', audio: 'IHB_IHP_5_22', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '7', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '22', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_BP/IHB_IHP_5_22.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_BP/IHB_IHP_5_30.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'NA', test_part: 'BP_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'BP_test', audio: 'IHB_IHP_5_30', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '7', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '30', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_BP/IHB_IHP_5_30.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_BP/UHB_UHP_5_0.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'NA', test_part: 'BP_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'BP_test', audio: 'UHB_UHP_5_0', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '7', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '0', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_BP/UHB_UHP_5_0.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_BP/UHB_UHP_5_2.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'NA', test_part: 'BP_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'BP_test', audio: 'UHB_UHP_5_2', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '7', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '2', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_BP/UHB_UHP_5_2.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_BP/UHB_UHP_5_4.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'NA', test_part: 'BP_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'BP_test', audio: 'UHB_UHP_5_4', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '7', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '4', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_BP/UHB_UHP_5_4.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_BP/UHB_UHP_5_5.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'NA', test_part: 'BP_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'BP_test', audio: 'UHB_UHP_5_5', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '7', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '5', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_BP/UHB_UHP_5_5.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_BP/UHB_UHP_5_6.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'NA', test_part: 'BP_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'BP_test', audio: 'UHB_UHP_5_6', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '7', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '6', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_BP/UHB_UHP_5_6.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_BP/UHB_UHP_5_7.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'NA', test_part: 'BP_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'BP_test', audio: 'UHB_UHP_5_7', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '7', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '7', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_BP/UHB_UHP_5_7.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_BP/UHB_UHP_5_9.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'NA', test_part: 'BP_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'BP_test', audio: 'UHB_UHP_5_9', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '7', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '9', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_BP/UHB_UHP_5_9.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_BP/UHB_UHP_5_11.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'NA', test_part: 'BP_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'BP_test', audio: 'UHB_UHP_5_11', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '7', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '11', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_BP/UHB_UHP_5_11.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_BP/UHB_UHP_5_15.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'NA', test_part: 'BP_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'BP_test', audio: 'UHB_UHP_5_15', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '7', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '15', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_BP/UHB_UHP_5_15.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_BP/UHB_UHP_5_21.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'NA', test_part: 'BP_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'BP_test', audio: 'UHB_UHP_5_21', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '7', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '21', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_BP/UHB_UHP_5_21.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_BP/UHB_UHP_5_30.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'NA', test_part: 'BP_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'BP_test', audio: 'UHB_UHP_5_30', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '7', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '30', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_BP/UHB_UHP_5_30.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_BP/AAB_AAP_1_0.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'NA', test_part: 'BP_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'BP_test', audio: 'AAB_AAP_1_0', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '0', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_BP/AAB_AAP_1_0.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_BP/AAB_AAP_1_3.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'NA', test_part: 'BP_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'BP_test', audio: 'AAB_AAP_1_3', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '3', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_BP/AAB_AAP_1_3.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_BP/AAB_AAP_1_5.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'NA', test_part: 'BP_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'BP_test', audio: 'AAB_AAP_1_5', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '5', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_BP/AAB_AAP_1_5.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_BP/AAB_AAP_1_7.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'NA', test_part: 'BP_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'BP_test', audio: 'AAB_AAP_1_7', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '7', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_BP/AAB_AAP_1_7.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_BP/AAB_AAP_1_9.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'NA', test_part: 'BP_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'BP_test', audio: 'AAB_AAP_1_9', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '9', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_BP/AAB_AAP_1_9.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_BP/AAB_AAP_1_10.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'NA', test_part: 'BP_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'BP_test', audio: 'AAB_AAP_1_10', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '10', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_BP/AAB_AAP_1_10.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_BP/AAB_AAP_1_11.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'NA', test_part: 'BP_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'BP_test', audio: 'AAB_AAP_1_11', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '11', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_BP/AAB_AAP_1_11.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_BP/AAB_AAP_1_13.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'NA', test_part: 'BP_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'BP_test', audio: 'AAB_AAP_1_13', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '13', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_BP/AAB_AAP_1_13.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_BP/AAB_AAP_1_17.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'NA', test_part: 'BP_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'BP_test', audio: 'AAB_AAP_1_17', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '17', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_BP/AAB_AAP_1_17.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_BP/AAB_AAP_1_23.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'NA', test_part: 'BP_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'BP_test', audio: 'AAB_AAP_1_23', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '23', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_BP/AAB_AAP_1_23.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_BP/AAB_AAP_1_30.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'NA', test_part: 'BP_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'BP_test', audio: 'AAB_AAP_1_30', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '30', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_BP/AAB_AAP_1_30.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_BP/AHB_AHP_3_0.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'NA', test_part: 'BP_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'BP_test', audio: 'AHB_AHP_3_0', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '0', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_BP/AHB_AHP_3_0.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_BP/AHB_AHP_3_3.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'NA', test_part: 'BP_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'BP_test', audio: 'AHB_AHP_3_3', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '3', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_BP/AHB_AHP_3_3.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_BP/AHB_AHP_3_5.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'NA', test_part: 'BP_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'BP_test', audio: 'AHB_AHP_3_5', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '5', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_BP/AHB_AHP_3_5.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_BP/AHB_AHP_3_7.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'NA', test_part: 'BP_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'BP_test', audio: 'AHB_AHP_3_7', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '7', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_BP/AHB_AHP_3_7.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_BP/AHB_AHP_3_9.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'NA', test_part: 'BP_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'BP_test', audio: 'AHB_AHP_3_9', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '9', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_BP/AHB_AHP_3_9.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_BP/AHB_AHP_3_10.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'NA', test_part: 'BP_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'BP_test', audio: 'AHB_AHP_3_10', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '10', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_BP/AHB_AHP_3_10.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_BP/AHB_AHP_3_11.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'NA', test_part: 'BP_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'BP_test', audio: 'AHB_AHP_3_11', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '11', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_BP/AHB_AHP_3_11.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_BP/AHB_AHP_3_13.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'NA', test_part: 'BP_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'BP_test', audio: 'AHB_AHP_3_13', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '13', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_BP/AHB_AHP_3_13.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_BP/AHB_AHP_3_17.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'NA', test_part: 'BP_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'BP_test', audio: 'AHB_AHP_3_17', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '17', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_BP/AHB_AHP_3_17.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_BP/AHB_AHP_3_23.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'NA', test_part: 'BP_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'BP_test', audio: 'AHB_AHP_3_23', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '23', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_BP/AHB_AHP_3_23.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_BP/AHB_AHP_3_30.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'NA', test_part: 'BP_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'BP_test', audio: 'AHB_AHP_3_30', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '30', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_BP/AHB_AHP_3_30.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_BP/IHB_IHP_5_0.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'NA', test_part: 'BP_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'BP_test', audio: 'IHB_IHP_5_0', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '7', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '0', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_BP/IHB_IHP_5_0.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_BP/IHB_IHP_5_2.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'NA', test_part: 'BP_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'BP_test', audio: 'IHB_IHP_5_2', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '7', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '2', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_BP/IHB_IHP_5_2.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_BP/IHB_IHP_5_4.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'NA', test_part: 'BP_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'BP_test', audio: 'IHB_IHP_5_4', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '7', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '4', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_BP/IHB_IHP_5_4.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_BP/IHB_IHP_5_5.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'NA', test_part: 'BP_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'BP_test', audio: 'IHB_IHP_5_5', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '7', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '5', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_BP/IHB_IHP_5_5.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_BP/IHB_IHP_5_6.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'NA', test_part: 'BP_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'BP_test', audio: 'IHB_IHP_5_6', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '7', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '6', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_BP/IHB_IHP_5_6.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_BP/IHB_IHP_5_7.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'NA', test_part: 'BP_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'BP_test', audio: 'IHB_IHP_5_7', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '7', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '7', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_BP/IHB_IHP_5_7.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_BP/IHB_IHP_5_9.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'NA', test_part: 'BP_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'BP_test', audio: 'IHB_IHP_5_9', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '7', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '9', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_BP/IHB_IHP_5_9.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_BP/IHB_IHP_5_11.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'NA', test_part: 'BP_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'BP_test', audio: 'IHB_IHP_5_11', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '7', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '11', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_BP/IHB_IHP_5_11.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_BP/IHB_IHP_5_15.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'NA', test_part: 'BP_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'BP_test', audio: 'IHB_IHP_5_15', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '7', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '15', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_BP/IHB_IHP_5_15.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_BP/IHB_IHP_5_22.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'NA', test_part: 'BP_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'BP_test', audio: 'IHB_IHP_5_22', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '7', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '22', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_BP/IHB_IHP_5_22.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_BP/IHB_IHP_5_30.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'NA', test_part: 'BP_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'BP_test', audio: 'IHB_IHP_5_30', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '7', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '30', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_BP/IHB_IHP_5_30.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_BP/UHB_UHP_5_0.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'NA', test_part: 'BP_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'BP_test', audio: 'UHB_UHP_5_0', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '7', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '0', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_BP/UHB_UHP_5_0.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_BP/UHB_UHP_5_2.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'NA', test_part: 'BP_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'BP_test', audio: 'UHB_UHP_5_2', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '7', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '2', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_BP/UHB_UHP_5_2.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_BP/UHB_UHP_5_4.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'NA', test_part: 'BP_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'BP_test', audio: 'UHB_UHP_5_4', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '7', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '4', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_BP/UHB_UHP_5_4.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_BP/UHB_UHP_5_5.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'NA', test_part: 'BP_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'BP_test', audio: 'UHB_UHP_5_5', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '7', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '5', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_BP/UHB_UHP_5_5.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_BP/UHB_UHP_5_6.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'NA', test_part: 'BP_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'BP_test', audio: 'UHB_UHP_5_6', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '7', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '6', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_BP/UHB_UHP_5_6.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_BP/UHB_UHP_5_7.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'NA', test_part: 'BP_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'BP_test', audio: 'UHB_UHP_5_7', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '7', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '7', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_BP/UHB_UHP_5_7.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_BP/UHB_UHP_5_9.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'NA', test_part: 'BP_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'BP_test', audio: 'UHB_UHP_5_9', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '7', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '9', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_BP/UHB_UHP_5_9.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_BP/UHB_UHP_5_11.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'NA', test_part: 'BP_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'BP_test', audio: 'UHB_UHP_5_11', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '7', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '11', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_BP/UHB_UHP_5_11.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_BP/UHB_UHP_5_15.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'NA', test_part: 'BP_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'BP_test', audio: 'UHB_UHP_5_15', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '7', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '15', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_BP/UHB_UHP_5_15.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_BP/UHB_UHP_5_21.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'NA', test_part: 'BP_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'BP_test', audio: 'UHB_UHP_5_21', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '7', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '21', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_BP/UHB_UHP_5_21.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_BP/UHB_UHP_5_30.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'NA', test_part: 'BP_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'BP_test', audio: 'UHB_UHP_5_30', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '7', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '30', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_BP/UHB_UHP_5_30.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_BP/AAB_AAP_1_0.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'NA', test_part: 'BP_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'BP_test', audio: 'AAB_AAP_1_0', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '0', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_BP/AAB_AAP_1_0.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_BP/AAB_AAP_1_3.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'NA', test_part: 'BP_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'BP_test', audio: 'AAB_AAP_1_3', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '3', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_BP/AAB_AAP_1_3.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_BP/AAB_AAP_1_5.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'NA', test_part: 'BP_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'BP_test', audio: 'AAB_AAP_1_5', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '5', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_BP/AAB_AAP_1_5.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_BP/AAB_AAP_1_7.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'NA', test_part: 'BP_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'BP_test', audio: 'AAB_AAP_1_7', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '7', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_BP/AAB_AAP_1_7.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_BP/AAB_AAP_1_9.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'NA', test_part: 'BP_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'BP_test', audio: 'AAB_AAP_1_9', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '9', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_BP/AAB_AAP_1_9.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_BP/AAB_AAP_1_10.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'NA', test_part: 'BP_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'BP_test', audio: 'AAB_AAP_1_10', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '10', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_BP/AAB_AAP_1_10.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_BP/AAB_AAP_1_11.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'NA', test_part: 'BP_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'BP_test', audio: 'AAB_AAP_1_11', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '11', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_BP/AAB_AAP_1_11.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_BP/AAB_AAP_1_13.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'NA', test_part: 'BP_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'BP_test', audio: 'AAB_AAP_1_13', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '13', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_BP/AAB_AAP_1_13.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_BP/AAB_AAP_1_17.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'NA', test_part: 'BP_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'BP_test', audio: 'AAB_AAP_1_17', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '17', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_BP/AAB_AAP_1_17.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_BP/AAB_AAP_1_23.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'NA', test_part: 'BP_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'BP_test', audio: 'AAB_AAP_1_23', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '23', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_BP/AAB_AAP_1_23.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_BP/AAB_AAP_1_30.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'NA', test_part: 'BP_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'BP_test', audio: 'AAB_AAP_1_30', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '30', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_BP/AAB_AAP_1_30.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_BP/AHB_AHP_3_0.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'NA', test_part: 'BP_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'BP_test', audio: 'AHB_AHP_3_0', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '0', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_BP/AHB_AHP_3_0.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_BP/AHB_AHP_3_3.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'NA', test_part: 'BP_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'BP_test', audio: 'AHB_AHP_3_3', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '3', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_BP/AHB_AHP_3_3.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_BP/AHB_AHP_3_5.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'NA', test_part: 'BP_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'BP_test', audio: 'AHB_AHP_3_5', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '5', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_BP/AHB_AHP_3_5.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_BP/AHB_AHP_3_7.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'NA', test_part: 'BP_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'BP_test', audio: 'AHB_AHP_3_7', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '7', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_BP/AHB_AHP_3_7.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_BP/AHB_AHP_3_9.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'NA', test_part: 'BP_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'BP_test', audio: 'AHB_AHP_3_9', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '9', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_BP/AHB_AHP_3_9.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_BP/AHB_AHP_3_10.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'NA', test_part: 'BP_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'BP_test', audio: 'AHB_AHP_3_10', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '10', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_BP/AHB_AHP_3_10.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_BP/AHB_AHP_3_11.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'NA', test_part: 'BP_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'BP_test', audio: 'AHB_AHP_3_11', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '11', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_BP/AHB_AHP_3_11.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_BP/AHB_AHP_3_13.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'NA', test_part: 'BP_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'BP_test', audio: 'AHB_AHP_3_13', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '13', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_BP/AHB_AHP_3_13.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_BP/AHB_AHP_3_17.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'NA', test_part: 'BP_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'BP_test', audio: 'AHB_AHP_3_17', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '17', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_BP/AHB_AHP_3_17.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_BP/AHB_AHP_3_23.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'NA', test_part: 'BP_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'BP_test', audio: 'AHB_AHP_3_23', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '23', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_BP/AHB_AHP_3_23.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_BP/AHB_AHP_3_30.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'NA', test_part: 'BP_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'BP_test', audio: 'AHB_AHP_3_30', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '30', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_BP/AHB_AHP_3_30.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_BP/IHB_IHP_5_0.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'NA', test_part: 'BP_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'BP_test', audio: 'IHB_IHP_5_0', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '7', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '0', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_BP/IHB_IHP_5_0.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_BP/IHB_IHP_5_2.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'NA', test_part: 'BP_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'BP_test', audio: 'IHB_IHP_5_2', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '7', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '2', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_BP/IHB_IHP_5_2.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_BP/IHB_IHP_5_4.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'NA', test_part: 'BP_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'BP_test', audio: 'IHB_IHP_5_4', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '7', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '4', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_BP/IHB_IHP_5_4.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_BP/IHB_IHP_5_5.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'NA', test_part: 'BP_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'BP_test', audio: 'IHB_IHP_5_5', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '7', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '5', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_BP/IHB_IHP_5_5.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_BP/IHB_IHP_5_6.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'NA', test_part: 'BP_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'BP_test', audio: 'IHB_IHP_5_6', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '7', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '6', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_BP/IHB_IHP_5_6.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_BP/IHB_IHP_5_7.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'NA', test_part: 'BP_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'BP_test', audio: 'IHB_IHP_5_7', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '7', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '7', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_BP/IHB_IHP_5_7.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_BP/IHB_IHP_5_9.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'NA', test_part: 'BP_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'BP_test', audio: 'IHB_IHP_5_9', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '7', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '9', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_BP/IHB_IHP_5_9.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_BP/IHB_IHP_5_11.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'NA', test_part: 'BP_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'BP_test', audio: 'IHB_IHP_5_11', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '7', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '11', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_BP/IHB_IHP_5_11.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_BP/IHB_IHP_5_15.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'NA', test_part: 'BP_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'BP_test', audio: 'IHB_IHP_5_15', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '7', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '15', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_BP/IHB_IHP_5_15.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_BP/IHB_IHP_5_22.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'NA', test_part: 'BP_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'BP_test', audio: 'IHB_IHP_5_22', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '7', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '22', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_BP/IHB_IHP_5_22.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_BP/IHB_IHP_5_30.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'NA', test_part: 'BP_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'BP_test', audio: 'IHB_IHP_5_30', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '7', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '30', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_BP/IHB_IHP_5_30.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_BP/UHB_UHP_5_0.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'NA', test_part: 'BP_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'BP_test', audio: 'UHB_UHP_5_0', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '7', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '0', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_BP/UHB_UHP_5_0.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_BP/UHB_UHP_5_2.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'NA', test_part: 'BP_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'BP_test', audio: 'UHB_UHP_5_2', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '7', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '2', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_BP/UHB_UHP_5_2.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_BP/UHB_UHP_5_4.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'NA', test_part: 'BP_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'BP_test', audio: 'UHB_UHP_5_4', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '7', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '4', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_BP/UHB_UHP_5_4.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_BP/UHB_UHP_5_5.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'NA', test_part: 'BP_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'BP_test', audio: 'UHB_UHP_5_5', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '7', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '5', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_BP/UHB_UHP_5_5.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_BP/UHB_UHP_5_6.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'NA', test_part: 'BP_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'BP_test', audio: 'UHB_UHP_5_6', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '7', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '6', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_BP/UHB_UHP_5_6.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_BP/UHB_UHP_5_7.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'NA', test_part: 'BP_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'BP_test', audio: 'UHB_UHP_5_7', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '7', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '7', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_BP/UHB_UHP_5_7.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_BP/UHB_UHP_5_9.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'NA', test_part: 'BP_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'BP_test', audio: 'UHB_UHP_5_9', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '7', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '9', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_BP/UHB_UHP_5_9.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_BP/UHB_UHP_5_11.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'NA', test_part: 'BP_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'BP_test', audio: 'UHB_UHP_5_11', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '7', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '11', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_BP/UHB_UHP_5_11.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_BP/UHB_UHP_5_15.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'NA', test_part: 'BP_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'BP_test', audio: 'UHB_UHP_5_15', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '7', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '15', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_BP/UHB_UHP_5_15.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_BP/UHB_UHP_5_21.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'NA', test_part: 'BP_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'BP_test', audio: 'UHB_UHP_5_21', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '7', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '21', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_BP/UHB_UHP_5_21.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_BP/UHB_UHP_5_30.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'NA', test_part: 'BP_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'BP_test', audio: 'UHB_UHP_5_30', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '7', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '30', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_BP/UHB_UHP_5_30.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_BP/AAB_AAP_1_0.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'NA', test_part: 'BP_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'BP_test', audio: 'AAB_AAP_1_0', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '0', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_BP/AAB_AAP_1_0.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_BP/AAB_AAP_1_3.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'NA', test_part: 'BP_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'BP_test', audio: 'AAB_AAP_1_3', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '3', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_BP/AAB_AAP_1_3.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_BP/AAB_AAP_1_5.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'NA', test_part: 'BP_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'BP_test', audio: 'AAB_AAP_1_5', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '5', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_BP/AAB_AAP_1_5.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_BP/AAB_AAP_1_7.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'NA', test_part: 'BP_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'BP_test', audio: 'AAB_AAP_1_7', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '7', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_BP/AAB_AAP_1_7.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_BP/AAB_AAP_1_9.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'NA', test_part: 'BP_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'BP_test', audio: 'AAB_AAP_1_9', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '9', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_BP/AAB_AAP_1_9.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_BP/AAB_AAP_1_10.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'NA', test_part: 'BP_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'BP_test', audio: 'AAB_AAP_1_10', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '10', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_BP/AAB_AAP_1_10.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_BP/AAB_AAP_1_11.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'NA', test_part: 'BP_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'BP_test', audio: 'AAB_AAP_1_11', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '11', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_BP/AAB_AAP_1_11.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_BP/AAB_AAP_1_13.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'NA', test_part: 'BP_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'BP_test', audio: 'AAB_AAP_1_13', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '13', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_BP/AAB_AAP_1_13.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_BP/AAB_AAP_1_17.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'NA', test_part: 'BP_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'BP_test', audio: 'AAB_AAP_1_17', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '17', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_BP/AAB_AAP_1_17.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_BP/AAB_AAP_1_23.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'NA', test_part: 'BP_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'BP_test', audio: 'AAB_AAP_1_23', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '23', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_BP/AAB_AAP_1_23.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_BP/AAB_AAP_1_30.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'NA', test_part: 'BP_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'BP_test', audio: 'AAB_AAP_1_30', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '30', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_BP/AAB_AAP_1_30.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_BP/AHB_AHP_3_0.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'NA', test_part: 'BP_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'BP_test', audio: 'AHB_AHP_3_0', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '0', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_BP/AHB_AHP_3_0.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_BP/AHB_AHP_3_3.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'NA', test_part: 'BP_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'BP_test', audio: 'AHB_AHP_3_3', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '3', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_BP/AHB_AHP_3_3.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_BP/AHB_AHP_3_5.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'NA', test_part: 'BP_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'BP_test', audio: 'AHB_AHP_3_5', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '5', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_BP/AHB_AHP_3_5.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_BP/AHB_AHP_3_7.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'NA', test_part: 'BP_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'BP_test', audio: 'AHB_AHP_3_7', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '7', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_BP/AHB_AHP_3_7.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_BP/AHB_AHP_3_9.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'NA', test_part: 'BP_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'BP_test', audio: 'AHB_AHP_3_9', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '9', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_BP/AHB_AHP_3_9.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_BP/AHB_AHP_3_10.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'NA', test_part: 'BP_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'BP_test', audio: 'AHB_AHP_3_10', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '10', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_BP/AHB_AHP_3_10.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_BP/AHB_AHP_3_11.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'NA', test_part: 'BP_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'BP_test', audio: 'AHB_AHP_3_11', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '11', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_BP/AHB_AHP_3_11.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_BP/AHB_AHP_3_13.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'NA', test_part: 'BP_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'BP_test', audio: 'AHB_AHP_3_13', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '13', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_BP/AHB_AHP_3_13.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_BP/AHB_AHP_3_17.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'NA', test_part: 'BP_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'BP_test', audio: 'AHB_AHP_3_17', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '17', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_BP/AHB_AHP_3_17.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_BP/AHB_AHP_3_23.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'NA', test_part: 'BP_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'BP_test', audio: 'AHB_AHP_3_23', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '23', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_BP/AHB_AHP_3_23.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_BP/AHB_AHP_3_30.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'NA', test_part: 'BP_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'BP_test', audio: 'AHB_AHP_3_30', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '30', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_BP/AHB_AHP_3_30.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_BP/IHB_IHP_5_0.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'NA', test_part: 'BP_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'BP_test', audio: 'IHB_IHP_5_0', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '7', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '0', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_BP/IHB_IHP_5_0.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_BP/IHB_IHP_5_2.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'NA', test_part: 'BP_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'BP_test', audio: 'IHB_IHP_5_2', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '7', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '2', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_BP/IHB_IHP_5_2.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_BP/IHB_IHP_5_4.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'NA', test_part: 'BP_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'BP_test', audio: 'IHB_IHP_5_4', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '7', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '4', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_BP/IHB_IHP_5_4.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_BP/IHB_IHP_5_5.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'NA', test_part: 'BP_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'BP_test', audio: 'IHB_IHP_5_5', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '7', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '5', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_BP/IHB_IHP_5_5.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_BP/IHB_IHP_5_6.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'NA', test_part: 'BP_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'BP_test', audio: 'IHB_IHP_5_6', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '7', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '6', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_BP/IHB_IHP_5_6.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_BP/IHB_IHP_5_7.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'NA', test_part: 'BP_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'BP_test', audio: 'IHB_IHP_5_7', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '7', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '7', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_BP/IHB_IHP_5_7.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_BP/IHB_IHP_5_9.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'NA', test_part: 'BP_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'BP_test', audio: 'IHB_IHP_5_9', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '7', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '9', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_BP/IHB_IHP_5_9.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_BP/IHB_IHP_5_11.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'NA', test_part: 'BP_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'BP_test', audio: 'IHB_IHP_5_11', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '7', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '11', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_BP/IHB_IHP_5_11.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_BP/IHB_IHP_5_15.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'NA', test_part: 'BP_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'BP_test', audio: 'IHB_IHP_5_15', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '7', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '15', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_BP/IHB_IHP_5_15.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_BP/IHB_IHP_5_22.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'NA', test_part: 'BP_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'BP_test', audio: 'IHB_IHP_5_22', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '7', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '22', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_BP/IHB_IHP_5_22.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_BP/IHB_IHP_5_30.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'NA', test_part: 'BP_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'BP_test', audio: 'IHB_IHP_5_30', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '7', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '30', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_BP/IHB_IHP_5_30.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_BP/UHB_UHP_5_0.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'NA', test_part: 'BP_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'BP_test', audio: 'UHB_UHP_5_0', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '7', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '0', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_BP/UHB_UHP_5_0.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_BP/UHB_UHP_5_2.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'NA', test_part: 'BP_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'BP_test', audio: 'UHB_UHP_5_2', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '7', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '2', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_BP/UHB_UHP_5_2.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_BP/UHB_UHP_5_4.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'NA', test_part: 'BP_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'BP_test', audio: 'UHB_UHP_5_4', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '7', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '4', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_BP/UHB_UHP_5_4.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_BP/UHB_UHP_5_5.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'NA', test_part: 'BP_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'BP_test', audio: 'UHB_UHP_5_5', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '7', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '5', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_BP/UHB_UHP_5_5.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_BP/UHB_UHP_5_6.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'NA', test_part: 'BP_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'BP_test', audio: 'UHB_UHP_5_6', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '7', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '6', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_BP/UHB_UHP_5_6.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_BP/UHB_UHP_5_7.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'NA', test_part: 'BP_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'BP_test', audio: 'UHB_UHP_5_7', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '7', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '7', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_BP/UHB_UHP_5_7.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_BP/UHB_UHP_5_9.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'NA', test_part: 'BP_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'BP_test', audio: 'UHB_UHP_5_9', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '7', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '9', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_BP/UHB_UHP_5_9.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_BP/UHB_UHP_5_11.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'NA', test_part: 'BP_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'BP_test', audio: 'UHB_UHP_5_11', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '7', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '11', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_BP/UHB_UHP_5_11.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_BP/UHB_UHP_5_15.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'NA', test_part: 'BP_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'BP_test', audio: 'UHB_UHP_5_15', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '7', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '15', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_BP/UHB_UHP_5_15.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_BP/UHB_UHP_5_21.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'NA', test_part: 'BP_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'BP_test', audio: 'UHB_UHP_5_21', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '7', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '21', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_BP/UHB_UHP_5_21.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_BP/UHB_UHP_5_30.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'NA', test_part: 'BP_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'BP_test', audio: 'UHB_UHP_5_30', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '7', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '30', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_BP/UHB_UHP_5_30.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_BP/AAB_AAP_1_0.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'NA', test_part: 'BP_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'BP_test', audio: 'AAB_AAP_1_0', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '0', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_BP/AAB_AAP_1_0.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_BP/AAB_AAP_1_3.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'NA', test_part: 'BP_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'BP_test', audio: 'AAB_AAP_1_3', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '3', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_BP/AAB_AAP_1_3.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_BP/AAB_AAP_1_5.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'NA', test_part: 'BP_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'BP_test', audio: 'AAB_AAP_1_5', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '5', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_BP/AAB_AAP_1_5.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_BP/AAB_AAP_1_7.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'NA', test_part: 'BP_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'BP_test', audio: 'AAB_AAP_1_7', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '7', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_BP/AAB_AAP_1_7.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_BP/AAB_AAP_1_9.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'NA', test_part: 'BP_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'BP_test', audio: 'AAB_AAP_1_9', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '9', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_BP/AAB_AAP_1_9.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_BP/AAB_AAP_1_10.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'NA', test_part: 'BP_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'BP_test', audio: 'AAB_AAP_1_10', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '10', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_BP/AAB_AAP_1_10.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_BP/AAB_AAP_1_11.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'NA', test_part: 'BP_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'BP_test', audio: 'AAB_AAP_1_11', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '11', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_BP/AAB_AAP_1_11.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_BP/AAB_AAP_1_13.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'NA', test_part: 'BP_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'BP_test', audio: 'AAB_AAP_1_13', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '13', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_BP/AAB_AAP_1_13.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_BP/AAB_AAP_1_17.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'NA', test_part: 'BP_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'BP_test', audio: 'AAB_AAP_1_17', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '17', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_BP/AAB_AAP_1_17.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_BP/AAB_AAP_1_23.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'NA', test_part: 'BP_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'BP_test', audio: 'AAB_AAP_1_23', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '23', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_BP/AAB_AAP_1_23.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_BP/AAB_AAP_1_30.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'NA', test_part: 'BP_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'BP_test', audio: 'AAB_AAP_1_30', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '30', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_BP/AAB_AAP_1_30.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_BP/AHB_AHP_3_0.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'NA', test_part: 'BP_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'BP_test', audio: 'AHB_AHP_3_0', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '0', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_BP/AHB_AHP_3_0.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_BP/AHB_AHP_3_3.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'NA', test_part: 'BP_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'BP_test', audio: 'AHB_AHP_3_3', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '3', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_BP/AHB_AHP_3_3.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_BP/AHB_AHP_3_5.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'NA', test_part: 'BP_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'BP_test', audio: 'AHB_AHP_3_5', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '5', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_BP/AHB_AHP_3_5.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_BP/AHB_AHP_3_7.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'NA', test_part: 'BP_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'BP_test', audio: 'AHB_AHP_3_7', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '7', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_BP/AHB_AHP_3_7.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_BP/AHB_AHP_3_9.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'NA', test_part: 'BP_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'BP_test', audio: 'AHB_AHP_3_9', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '9', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_BP/AHB_AHP_3_9.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_BP/AHB_AHP_3_10.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'NA', test_part: 'BP_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'BP_test', audio: 'AHB_AHP_3_10', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '10', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_BP/AHB_AHP_3_10.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_BP/AHB_AHP_3_11.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'NA', test_part: 'BP_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'BP_test', audio: 'AHB_AHP_3_11', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '11', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_BP/AHB_AHP_3_11.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_BP/AHB_AHP_3_13.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'NA', test_part: 'BP_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'BP_test', audio: 'AHB_AHP_3_13', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '13', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_BP/AHB_AHP_3_13.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_BP/AHB_AHP_3_17.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'NA', test_part: 'BP_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'BP_test', audio: 'AHB_AHP_3_17', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '17', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_BP/AHB_AHP_3_17.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_BP/AHB_AHP_3_23.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'NA', test_part: 'BP_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'BP_test', audio: 'AHB_AHP_3_23', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '23', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_BP/AHB_AHP_3_23.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_BP/AHB_AHP_3_30.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'NA', test_part: 'BP_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'BP_test', audio: 'AHB_AHP_3_30', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '30', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_BP/AHB_AHP_3_30.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_BP/IHB_IHP_5_0.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'NA', test_part: 'BP_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'BP_test', audio: 'IHB_IHP_5_0', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '7', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '0', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_BP/IHB_IHP_5_0.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_BP/IHB_IHP_5_2.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'NA', test_part: 'BP_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'BP_test', audio: 'IHB_IHP_5_2', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '7', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '2', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_BP/IHB_IHP_5_2.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_BP/IHB_IHP_5_4.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'NA', test_part: 'BP_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'BP_test', audio: 'IHB_IHP_5_4', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '7', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '4', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_BP/IHB_IHP_5_4.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_BP/IHB_IHP_5_5.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'NA', test_part: 'BP_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'BP_test', audio: 'IHB_IHP_5_5', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '7', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '5', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_BP/IHB_IHP_5_5.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_BP/IHB_IHP_5_6.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'NA', test_part: 'BP_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'BP_test', audio: 'IHB_IHP_5_6', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '7', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '6', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_BP/IHB_IHP_5_6.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_BP/IHB_IHP_5_7.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'NA', test_part: 'BP_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'BP_test', audio: 'IHB_IHP_5_7', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '7', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '7', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_BP/IHB_IHP_5_7.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_BP/IHB_IHP_5_9.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'NA', test_part: 'BP_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'BP_test', audio: 'IHB_IHP_5_9', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '7', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '9', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_BP/IHB_IHP_5_9.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_BP/IHB_IHP_5_11.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'NA', test_part: 'BP_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'BP_test', audio: 'IHB_IHP_5_11', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '7', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '11', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_BP/IHB_IHP_5_11.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_BP/IHB_IHP_5_15.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'NA', test_part: 'BP_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'BP_test', audio: 'IHB_IHP_5_15', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '7', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '15', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_BP/IHB_IHP_5_15.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_BP/IHB_IHP_5_22.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'NA', test_part: 'BP_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'BP_test', audio: 'IHB_IHP_5_22', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '7', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '22', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_BP/IHB_IHP_5_22.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_BP/IHB_IHP_5_30.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'NA', test_part: 'BP_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'BP_test', audio: 'IHB_IHP_5_30', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '7', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '30', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_BP/IHB_IHP_5_30.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_BP/UHB_UHP_5_0.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'NA', test_part: 'BP_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'BP_test', audio: 'UHB_UHP_5_0', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '7', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '0', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_BP/UHB_UHP_5_0.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_BP/UHB_UHP_5_2.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'NA', test_part: 'BP_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'BP_test', audio: 'UHB_UHP_5_2', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '7', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '2', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_BP/UHB_UHP_5_2.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_BP/UHB_UHP_5_4.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'NA', test_part: 'BP_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'BP_test', audio: 'UHB_UHP_5_4', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '7', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '4', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_BP/UHB_UHP_5_4.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_BP/UHB_UHP_5_5.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'NA', test_part: 'BP_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'BP_test', audio: 'UHB_UHP_5_5', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '7', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '5', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_BP/UHB_UHP_5_5.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_BP/UHB_UHP_5_6.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'NA', test_part: 'BP_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'BP_test', audio: 'UHB_UHP_5_6', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '7', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '6', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_BP/UHB_UHP_5_6.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_BP/UHB_UHP_5_7.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'NA', test_part: 'BP_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'BP_test', audio: 'UHB_UHP_5_7', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '7', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '7', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_BP/UHB_UHP_5_7.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_BP/UHB_UHP_5_9.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'NA', test_part: 'BP_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'BP_test', audio: 'UHB_UHP_5_9', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '7', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '9', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_BP/UHB_UHP_5_9.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_BP/UHB_UHP_5_11.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'NA', test_part: 'BP_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'BP_test', audio: 'UHB_UHP_5_11', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '7', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '11', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_BP/UHB_UHP_5_11.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_BP/UHB_UHP_5_15.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'NA', test_part: 'BP_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'BP_test', audio: 'UHB_UHP_5_15', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '7', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '15', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_BP/UHB_UHP_5_15.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_BP/UHB_UHP_5_21.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'NA', test_part: 'BP_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'BP_test', audio: 'UHB_UHP_5_21', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '7', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '21', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_BP/UHB_UHP_5_21.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_BP/UHB_UHP_5_30.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'NA', test_part: 'BP_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'BP_test', audio: 'UHB_UHP_5_30', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '7', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '30', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_BP/UHB_UHP_5_30.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_BP/AAB_AAP_1_0.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'NA', test_part: 'BP_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'BP_test', audio: 'AAB_AAP_1_0', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '0', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_BP/AAB_AAP_1_0.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_BP/AAB_AAP_1_3.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'NA', test_part: 'BP_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'BP_test', audio: 'AAB_AAP_1_3', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '3', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_BP/AAB_AAP_1_3.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_BP/AAB_AAP_1_5.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'NA', test_part: 'BP_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'BP_test', audio: 'AAB_AAP_1_5', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '5', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_BP/AAB_AAP_1_5.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_BP/AAB_AAP_1_7.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'NA', test_part: 'BP_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'BP_test', audio: 'AAB_AAP_1_7', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '7', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_BP/AAB_AAP_1_7.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_BP/AAB_AAP_1_9.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'NA', test_part: 'BP_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'BP_test', audio: 'AAB_AAP_1_9', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '9', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_BP/AAB_AAP_1_9.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_BP/AAB_AAP_1_10.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'NA', test_part: 'BP_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'BP_test', audio: 'AAB_AAP_1_10', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '10', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_BP/AAB_AAP_1_10.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_BP/AAB_AAP_1_11.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'NA', test_part: 'BP_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'BP_test', audio: 'AAB_AAP_1_11', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '11', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_BP/AAB_AAP_1_11.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_BP/AAB_AAP_1_13.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'NA', test_part: 'BP_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'BP_test', audio: 'AAB_AAP_1_13', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '13', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_BP/AAB_AAP_1_13.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_BP/AAB_AAP_1_17.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'NA', test_part: 'BP_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'BP_test', audio: 'AAB_AAP_1_17', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '17', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_BP/AAB_AAP_1_17.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_BP/AAB_AAP_1_23.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'NA', test_part: 'BP_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'BP_test', audio: 'AAB_AAP_1_23', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '23', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_BP/AAB_AAP_1_23.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_BP/AAB_AAP_1_30.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'NA', test_part: 'BP_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'BP_test', audio: 'AAB_AAP_1_30', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '30', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_BP/AAB_AAP_1_30.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_BP/AHB_AHP_3_0.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'NA', test_part: 'BP_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'BP_test', audio: 'AHB_AHP_3_0', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '0', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_BP/AHB_AHP_3_0.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_BP/AHB_AHP_3_3.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'NA', test_part: 'BP_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'BP_test', audio: 'AHB_AHP_3_3', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '3', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_BP/AHB_AHP_3_3.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_BP/AHB_AHP_3_5.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'NA', test_part: 'BP_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'BP_test', audio: 'AHB_AHP_3_5', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '5', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_BP/AHB_AHP_3_5.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_BP/AHB_AHP_3_7.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'NA', test_part: 'BP_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'BP_test', audio: 'AHB_AHP_3_7', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '7', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_BP/AHB_AHP_3_7.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_BP/AHB_AHP_3_9.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'NA', test_part: 'BP_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'BP_test', audio: 'AHB_AHP_3_9', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '9', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_BP/AHB_AHP_3_9.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_BP/AHB_AHP_3_10.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'NA', test_part: 'BP_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'BP_test', audio: 'AHB_AHP_3_10', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '10', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_BP/AHB_AHP_3_10.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_BP/AHB_AHP_3_11.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'NA', test_part: 'BP_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'BP_test', audio: 'AHB_AHP_3_11', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '11', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_BP/AHB_AHP_3_11.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_BP/AHB_AHP_3_13.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'NA', test_part: 'BP_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'BP_test', audio: 'AHB_AHP_3_13', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '13', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_BP/AHB_AHP_3_13.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_BP/AHB_AHP_3_17.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'NA', test_part: 'BP_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'BP_test', audio: 'AHB_AHP_3_17', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '17', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_BP/AHB_AHP_3_17.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_BP/AHB_AHP_3_23.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'NA', test_part: 'BP_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'BP_test', audio: 'AHB_AHP_3_23', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '23', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_BP/AHB_AHP_3_23.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_BP/AHB_AHP_3_30.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'NA', test_part: 'BP_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'BP_test', audio: 'AHB_AHP_3_30', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '30', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_BP/AHB_AHP_3_30.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_BP/IHB_IHP_5_0.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'NA', test_part: 'BP_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'BP_test', audio: 'IHB_IHP_5_0', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '7', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '0', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_BP/IHB_IHP_5_0.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_BP/IHB_IHP_5_2.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'NA', test_part: 'BP_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'BP_test', audio: 'IHB_IHP_5_2', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '7', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '2', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_BP/IHB_IHP_5_2.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_BP/IHB_IHP_5_4.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'NA', test_part: 'BP_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'BP_test', audio: 'IHB_IHP_5_4', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '7', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '4', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_BP/IHB_IHP_5_4.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_BP/IHB_IHP_5_5.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'NA', test_part: 'BP_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'BP_test', audio: 'IHB_IHP_5_5', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '7', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '5', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_BP/IHB_IHP_5_5.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_BP/IHB_IHP_5_6.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'NA', test_part: 'BP_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'BP_test', audio: 'IHB_IHP_5_6', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '7', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '6', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_BP/IHB_IHP_5_6.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_BP/IHB_IHP_5_7.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'NA', test_part: 'BP_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'BP_test', audio: 'IHB_IHP_5_7', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '7', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '7', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_BP/IHB_IHP_5_7.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_BP/IHB_IHP_5_9.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'NA', test_part: 'BP_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'BP_test', audio: 'IHB_IHP_5_9', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '7', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '9', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_BP/IHB_IHP_5_9.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_BP/IHB_IHP_5_11.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'NA', test_part: 'BP_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'BP_test', audio: 'IHB_IHP_5_11', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '7', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '11', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_BP/IHB_IHP_5_11.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_BP/IHB_IHP_5_15.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'NA', test_part: 'BP_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'BP_test', audio: 'IHB_IHP_5_15', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '7', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '15', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_BP/IHB_IHP_5_15.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_BP/IHB_IHP_5_22.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'NA', test_part: 'BP_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'BP_test', audio: 'IHB_IHP_5_22', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '7', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '22', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_BP/IHB_IHP_5_22.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_BP/IHB_IHP_5_30.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'NA', test_part: 'BP_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'BP_test', audio: 'IHB_IHP_5_30', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '7', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '30', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_BP/IHB_IHP_5_30.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_BP/UHB_UHP_5_0.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'NA', test_part: 'BP_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'BP_test', audio: 'UHB_UHP_5_0', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '7', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '0', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_BP/UHB_UHP_5_0.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_BP/UHB_UHP_5_2.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'NA', test_part: 'BP_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'BP_test', audio: 'UHB_UHP_5_2', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '7', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '2', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_BP/UHB_UHP_5_2.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_BP/UHB_UHP_5_4.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'NA', test_part: 'BP_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'BP_test', audio: 'UHB_UHP_5_4', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '7', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '4', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_BP/UHB_UHP_5_4.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_BP/UHB_UHP_5_5.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'NA', test_part: 'BP_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'BP_test', audio: 'UHB_UHP_5_5', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '7', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '5', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_BP/UHB_UHP_5_5.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_BP/UHB_UHP_5_6.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'NA', test_part: 'BP_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'BP_test', audio: 'UHB_UHP_5_6', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '7', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '6', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_BP/UHB_UHP_5_6.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_BP/UHB_UHP_5_7.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'NA', test_part: 'BP_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'BP_test', audio: 'UHB_UHP_5_7', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '7', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '7', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_BP/UHB_UHP_5_7.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_BP/UHB_UHP_5_9.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'NA', test_part: 'BP_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'BP_test', audio: 'UHB_UHP_5_9', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '7', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '9', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_BP/UHB_UHP_5_9.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_BP/UHB_UHP_5_11.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'NA', test_part: 'BP_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'BP_test', audio: 'UHB_UHP_5_11', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '7', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '11', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_BP/UHB_UHP_5_11.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_BP/UHB_UHP_5_15.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'NA', test_part: 'BP_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'BP_test', audio: 'UHB_UHP_5_15', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '7', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '15', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_BP/UHB_UHP_5_15.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_BP/UHB_UHP_5_21.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'NA', test_part: 'BP_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'BP_test', audio: 'UHB_UHP_5_21', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '7', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '21', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_BP/UHB_UHP_5_21.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_BP/UHB_UHP_5_30.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'NA', test_part: 'BP_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'BP_test', audio: 'UHB_UHP_5_30', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '7', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '30', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_BP/UHB_UHP_5_30.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_BP/AAB_AAP_1_0.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'NA', test_part: 'BP_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'BP_test', audio: 'AAB_AAP_1_0', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '0', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_BP/AAB_AAP_1_0.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_BP/AAB_AAP_1_3.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'NA', test_part: 'BP_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'BP_test', audio: 'AAB_AAP_1_3', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '3', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_BP/AAB_AAP_1_3.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_BP/AAB_AAP_1_5.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'NA', test_part: 'BP_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'BP_test', audio: 'AAB_AAP_1_5', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '5', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_BP/AAB_AAP_1_5.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_BP/AAB_AAP_1_7.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'NA', test_part: 'BP_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'BP_test', audio: 'AAB_AAP_1_7', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '7', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_BP/AAB_AAP_1_7.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_BP/AAB_AAP_1_9.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'NA', test_part: 'BP_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'BP_test', audio: 'AAB_AAP_1_9', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '9', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_BP/AAB_AAP_1_9.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_BP/AAB_AAP_1_10.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'NA', test_part: 'BP_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'BP_test', audio: 'AAB_AAP_1_10', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '10', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_BP/AAB_AAP_1_10.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_BP/AAB_AAP_1_11.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'NA', test_part: 'BP_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'BP_test', audio: 'AAB_AAP_1_11', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '11', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_BP/AAB_AAP_1_11.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_BP/AAB_AAP_1_13.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'NA', test_part: 'BP_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'BP_test', audio: 'AAB_AAP_1_13', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '13', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_BP/AAB_AAP_1_13.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_BP/AAB_AAP_1_17.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'NA', test_part: 'BP_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'BP_test', audio: 'AAB_AAP_1_17', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '17', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_BP/AAB_AAP_1_17.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_BP/AAB_AAP_1_23.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'NA', test_part: 'BP_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'BP_test', audio: 'AAB_AAP_1_23', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '23', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_BP/AAB_AAP_1_23.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_BP/AAB_AAP_1_30.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'NA', test_part: 'BP_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'BP_test', audio: 'AAB_AAP_1_30', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '30', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_BP/AAB_AAP_1_30.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_BP/AHB_AHP_3_0.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'NA', test_part: 'BP_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'BP_test', audio: 'AHB_AHP_3_0', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '0', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_BP/AHB_AHP_3_0.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_BP/AHB_AHP_3_3.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'NA', test_part: 'BP_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'BP_test', audio: 'AHB_AHP_3_3', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '3', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_BP/AHB_AHP_3_3.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_BP/AHB_AHP_3_5.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'NA', test_part: 'BP_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'BP_test', audio: 'AHB_AHP_3_5', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '5', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_BP/AHB_AHP_3_5.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_BP/AHB_AHP_3_7.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'NA', test_part: 'BP_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'BP_test', audio: 'AHB_AHP_3_7', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '7', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_BP/AHB_AHP_3_7.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_BP/AHB_AHP_3_9.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'NA', test_part: 'BP_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'BP_test', audio: 'AHB_AHP_3_9', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '9', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_BP/AHB_AHP_3_9.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_BP/AHB_AHP_3_10.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'NA', test_part: 'BP_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'BP_test', audio: 'AHB_AHP_3_10', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '10', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_BP/AHB_AHP_3_10.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_BP/AHB_AHP_3_11.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'NA', test_part: 'BP_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'BP_test', audio: 'AHB_AHP_3_11', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '11', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_BP/AHB_AHP_3_11.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_BP/AHB_AHP_3_13.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'NA', test_part: 'BP_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'BP_test', audio: 'AHB_AHP_3_13', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '13', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_BP/AHB_AHP_3_13.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_BP/AHB_AHP_3_17.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'NA', test_part: 'BP_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'BP_test', audio: 'AHB_AHP_3_17', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '17', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_BP/AHB_AHP_3_17.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_BP/AHB_AHP_3_23.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'NA', test_part: 'BP_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'BP_test', audio: 'AHB_AHP_3_23', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '23', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_BP/AHB_AHP_3_23.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_BP/AHB_AHP_3_30.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'NA', test_part: 'BP_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'BP_test', audio: 'AHB_AHP_3_30', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '30', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_BP/AHB_AHP_3_30.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_BP/IHB_IHP_5_0.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'NA', test_part: 'BP_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'BP_test', audio: 'IHB_IHP_5_0', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '7', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '0', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_BP/IHB_IHP_5_0.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_BP/IHB_IHP_5_2.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'NA', test_part: 'BP_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'BP_test', audio: 'IHB_IHP_5_2', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '7', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '2', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_BP/IHB_IHP_5_2.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_BP/IHB_IHP_5_4.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'NA', test_part: 'BP_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'BP_test', audio: 'IHB_IHP_5_4', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '7', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '4', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_BP/IHB_IHP_5_4.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_BP/IHB_IHP_5_5.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'NA', test_part: 'BP_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'BP_test', audio: 'IHB_IHP_5_5', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '7', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '5', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_BP/IHB_IHP_5_5.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_BP/IHB_IHP_5_6.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'NA', test_part: 'BP_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'BP_test', audio: 'IHB_IHP_5_6', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '7', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '6', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_BP/IHB_IHP_5_6.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_BP/IHB_IHP_5_7.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'NA', test_part: 'BP_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'BP_test', audio: 'IHB_IHP_5_7', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '7', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '7', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_BP/IHB_IHP_5_7.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_BP/IHB_IHP_5_9.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'NA', test_part: 'BP_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'BP_test', audio: 'IHB_IHP_5_9', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '7', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '9', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_BP/IHB_IHP_5_9.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_BP/IHB_IHP_5_11.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'NA', test_part: 'BP_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'BP_test', audio: 'IHB_IHP_5_11', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '7', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '11', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_BP/IHB_IHP_5_11.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_BP/IHB_IHP_5_15.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'NA', test_part: 'BP_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'BP_test', audio: 'IHB_IHP_5_15', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '7', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '15', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_BP/IHB_IHP_5_15.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_BP/IHB_IHP_5_22.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'NA', test_part: 'BP_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'BP_test', audio: 'IHB_IHP_5_22', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '7', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '22', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_BP/IHB_IHP_5_22.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_BP/IHB_IHP_5_30.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'NA', test_part: 'BP_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'BP_test', audio: 'IHB_IHP_5_30', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '7', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '30', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_BP/IHB_IHP_5_30.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_BP/UHB_UHP_5_0.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'NA', test_part: 'BP_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'BP_test', audio: 'UHB_UHP_5_0', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '7', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '0', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_BP/UHB_UHP_5_0.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_BP/UHB_UHP_5_2.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'NA', test_part: 'BP_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'BP_test', audio: 'UHB_UHP_5_2', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '7', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '2', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_BP/UHB_UHP_5_2.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_BP/UHB_UHP_5_4.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'NA', test_part: 'BP_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'BP_test', audio: 'UHB_UHP_5_4', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '7', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '4', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_BP/UHB_UHP_5_4.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_BP/UHB_UHP_5_5.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'NA', test_part: 'BP_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'BP_test', audio: 'UHB_UHP_5_5', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '7', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '5', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_BP/UHB_UHP_5_5.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_BP/UHB_UHP_5_6.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'NA', test_part: 'BP_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'BP_test', audio: 'UHB_UHP_5_6', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '7', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '6', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_BP/UHB_UHP_5_6.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_BP/UHB_UHP_5_7.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'NA', test_part: 'BP_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'BP_test', audio: 'UHB_UHP_5_7', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '7', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '7', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_BP/UHB_UHP_5_7.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_BP/UHB_UHP_5_9.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'NA', test_part: 'BP_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'BP_test', audio: 'UHB_UHP_5_9', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '7', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '9', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_BP/UHB_UHP_5_9.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_BP/UHB_UHP_5_11.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'NA', test_part: 'BP_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'BP_test', audio: 'UHB_UHP_5_11', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '7', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '11', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_BP/UHB_UHP_5_11.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_BP/UHB_UHP_5_15.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'NA', test_part: 'BP_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'BP_test', audio: 'UHB_UHP_5_15', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '7', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '15', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_BP/UHB_UHP_5_15.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_BP/UHB_UHP_5_21.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'NA', test_part: 'BP_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'BP_test', audio: 'UHB_UHP_5_21', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '7', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '21', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_BP/UHB_UHP_5_21.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_BP/UHB_UHP_5_30.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'NA', test_part: 'BP_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'BP_test', audio: 'UHB_UHP_5_30', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '7', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '30', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_BP/UHB_UHP_5_30.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_BP/AAB_AAP_1_0.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'NA', test_part: 'BP_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'BP_test', audio: 'AAB_AAP_1_0', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '0', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_BP/AAB_AAP_1_0.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_BP/AAB_AAP_1_3.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'NA', test_part: 'BP_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'BP_test', audio: 'AAB_AAP_1_3', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '3', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_BP/AAB_AAP_1_3.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_BP/AAB_AAP_1_5.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'NA', test_part: 'BP_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'BP_test', audio: 'AAB_AAP_1_5', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '5', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_BP/AAB_AAP_1_5.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_BP/AAB_AAP_1_7.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'NA', test_part: 'BP_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'BP_test', audio: 'AAB_AAP_1_7', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '7', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_BP/AAB_AAP_1_7.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_BP/AAB_AAP_1_9.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'NA', test_part: 'BP_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'BP_test', audio: 'AAB_AAP_1_9', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '9', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_BP/AAB_AAP_1_9.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_BP/AAB_AAP_1_10.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'NA', test_part: 'BP_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'BP_test', audio: 'AAB_AAP_1_10', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '10', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_BP/AAB_AAP_1_10.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_BP/AAB_AAP_1_11.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'NA', test_part: 'BP_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'BP_test', audio: 'AAB_AAP_1_11', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '11', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_BP/AAB_AAP_1_11.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_BP/AAB_AAP_1_13.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'NA', test_part: 'BP_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'BP_test', audio: 'AAB_AAP_1_13', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '13', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_BP/AAB_AAP_1_13.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_BP/AAB_AAP_1_17.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'NA', test_part: 'BP_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'BP_test', audio: 'AAB_AAP_1_17', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '17', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_BP/AAB_AAP_1_17.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_BP/AAB_AAP_1_23.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'NA', test_part: 'BP_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'BP_test', audio: 'AAB_AAP_1_23', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '23', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_BP/AAB_AAP_1_23.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_BP/AAB_AAP_1_30.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'NA', test_part: 'BP_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'BP_test', audio: 'AAB_AAP_1_30', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '30', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_BP/AAB_AAP_1_30.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_BP/AHB_AHP_3_0.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'NA', test_part: 'BP_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'BP_test', audio: 'AHB_AHP_3_0', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '0', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_BP/AHB_AHP_3_0.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_BP/AHB_AHP_3_3.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'NA', test_part: 'BP_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'BP_test', audio: 'AHB_AHP_3_3', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '3', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_BP/AHB_AHP_3_3.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_BP/AHB_AHP_3_5.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'NA', test_part: 'BP_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'BP_test', audio: 'AHB_AHP_3_5', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '5', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_BP/AHB_AHP_3_5.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_BP/AHB_AHP_3_7.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'NA', test_part: 'BP_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'BP_test', audio: 'AHB_AHP_3_7', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '7', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_BP/AHB_AHP_3_7.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_BP/AHB_AHP_3_9.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'NA', test_part: 'BP_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'BP_test', audio: 'AHB_AHP_3_9', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '9', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_BP/AHB_AHP_3_9.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_BP/AHB_AHP_3_10.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'NA', test_part: 'BP_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'BP_test', audio: 'AHB_AHP_3_10', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '10', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_BP/AHB_AHP_3_10.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_BP/AHB_AHP_3_11.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'NA', test_part: 'BP_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'BP_test', audio: 'AHB_AHP_3_11', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '11', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_BP/AHB_AHP_3_11.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_BP/AHB_AHP_3_13.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'NA', test_part: 'BP_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'BP_test', audio: 'AHB_AHP_3_13', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '13', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_BP/AHB_AHP_3_13.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_BP/AHB_AHP_3_17.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'NA', test_part: 'BP_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'BP_test', audio: 'AHB_AHP_3_17', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '17', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_BP/AHB_AHP_3_17.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_BP/AHB_AHP_3_23.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'NA', test_part: 'BP_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'BP_test', audio: 'AHB_AHP_3_23', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '23', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_BP/AHB_AHP_3_23.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_BP/AHB_AHP_3_30.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'NA', test_part: 'BP_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'BP_test', audio: 'AHB_AHP_3_30', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '30', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_BP/AHB_AHP_3_30.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_BP/IHB_IHP_5_0.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'NA', test_part: 'BP_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'BP_test', audio: 'IHB_IHP_5_0', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '7', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '0', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_BP/IHB_IHP_5_0.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_BP/IHB_IHP_5_2.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'NA', test_part: 'BP_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'BP_test', audio: 'IHB_IHP_5_2', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '7', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '2', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_BP/IHB_IHP_5_2.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_BP/IHB_IHP_5_4.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'NA', test_part: 'BP_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'BP_test', audio: 'IHB_IHP_5_4', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '7', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '4', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_BP/IHB_IHP_5_4.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_BP/IHB_IHP_5_5.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'NA', test_part: 'BP_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'BP_test', audio: 'IHB_IHP_5_5', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '7', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '5', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_BP/IHB_IHP_5_5.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_BP/IHB_IHP_5_6.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'NA', test_part: 'BP_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'BP_test', audio: 'IHB_IHP_5_6', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '7', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '6', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_BP/IHB_IHP_5_6.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_BP/IHB_IHP_5_7.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'NA', test_part: 'BP_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'BP_test', audio: 'IHB_IHP_5_7', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '7', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '7', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_BP/IHB_IHP_5_7.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_BP/IHB_IHP_5_9.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'NA', test_part: 'BP_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'BP_test', audio: 'IHB_IHP_5_9', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '7', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '9', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_BP/IHB_IHP_5_9.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_BP/IHB_IHP_5_11.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'NA', test_part: 'BP_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'BP_test', audio: 'IHB_IHP_5_11', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '7', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '11', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_BP/IHB_IHP_5_11.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_BP/IHB_IHP_5_15.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'NA', test_part: 'BP_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'BP_test', audio: 'IHB_IHP_5_15', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '7', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '15', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_BP/IHB_IHP_5_15.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_BP/IHB_IHP_5_22.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'NA', test_part: 'BP_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'BP_test', audio: 'IHB_IHP_5_22', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '7', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '22', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_BP/IHB_IHP_5_22.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_BP/IHB_IHP_5_30.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'NA', test_part: 'BP_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'BP_test', audio: 'IHB_IHP_5_30', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '7', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '30', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_BP/IHB_IHP_5_30.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_BP/UHB_UHP_5_0.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'NA', test_part: 'BP_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'BP_test', audio: 'UHB_UHP_5_0', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '7', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '0', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_BP/UHB_UHP_5_0.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_BP/UHB_UHP_5_2.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'NA', test_part: 'BP_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'BP_test', audio: 'UHB_UHP_5_2', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '7', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '2', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_BP/UHB_UHP_5_2.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_BP/UHB_UHP_5_4.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'NA', test_part: 'BP_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'BP_test', audio: 'UHB_UHP_5_4', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '7', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '4', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_BP/UHB_UHP_5_4.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_BP/UHB_UHP_5_5.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'NA', test_part: 'BP_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'BP_test', audio: 'UHB_UHP_5_5', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '7', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '5', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_BP/UHB_UHP_5_5.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_BP/UHB_UHP_5_6.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'NA', test_part: 'BP_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'BP_test', audio: 'UHB_UHP_5_6', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '7', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '6', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_BP/UHB_UHP_5_6.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_BP/UHB_UHP_5_7.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'NA', test_part: 'BP_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'BP_test', audio: 'UHB_UHP_5_7', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '7', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '7', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_BP/UHB_UHP_5_7.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_BP/UHB_UHP_5_9.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'NA', test_part: 'BP_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'BP_test', audio: 'UHB_UHP_5_9', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '7', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '9', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_BP/UHB_UHP_5_9.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_BP/UHB_UHP_5_11.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'NA', test_part: 'BP_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'BP_test', audio: 'UHB_UHP_5_11', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '7', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '11', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_BP/UHB_UHP_5_11.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_BP/UHB_UHP_5_15.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'NA', test_part: 'BP_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'BP_test', audio: 'UHB_UHP_5_15', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '7', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '15', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_BP/UHB_UHP_5_15.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_BP/UHB_UHP_5_21.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'NA', test_part: 'BP_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'BP_test', audio: 'UHB_UHP_5_21', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '7', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '21', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_BP/UHB_UHP_5_21.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_BP/UHB_UHP_5_30.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'NA', test_part: 'BP_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'BP_test', audio: 'UHB_UHP_5_30', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '7', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '30', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_BP/UHB_UHP_5_30.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_BP/AAB_AAP_1_0.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'NA', test_part: 'BP_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'BP_test', audio: 'AAB_AAP_1_0', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '0', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_BP/AAB_AAP_1_0.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_BP/AAB_AAP_1_3.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'NA', test_part: 'BP_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'BP_test', audio: 'AAB_AAP_1_3', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '3', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_BP/AAB_AAP_1_3.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_BP/AAB_AAP_1_5.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'NA', test_part: 'BP_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'BP_test', audio: 'AAB_AAP_1_5', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '5', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_BP/AAB_AAP_1_5.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_BP/AAB_AAP_1_7.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'NA', test_part: 'BP_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'BP_test', audio: 'AAB_AAP_1_7', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '7', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_BP/AAB_AAP_1_7.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_BP/AAB_AAP_1_9.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'NA', test_part: 'BP_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'BP_test', audio: 'AAB_AAP_1_9', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '9', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_BP/AAB_AAP_1_9.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_BP/AAB_AAP_1_10.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'NA', test_part: 'BP_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'BP_test', audio: 'AAB_AAP_1_10', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '10', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_BP/AAB_AAP_1_10.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_BP/AAB_AAP_1_11.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'NA', test_part: 'BP_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'BP_test', audio: 'AAB_AAP_1_11', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '11', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_BP/AAB_AAP_1_11.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_BP/AAB_AAP_1_13.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'NA', test_part: 'BP_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'BP_test', audio: 'AAB_AAP_1_13', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '13', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_BP/AAB_AAP_1_13.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_BP/AAB_AAP_1_17.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'NA', test_part: 'BP_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'BP_test', audio: 'AAB_AAP_1_17', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '17', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_BP/AAB_AAP_1_17.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_BP/AAB_AAP_1_23.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'NA', test_part: 'BP_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'BP_test', audio: 'AAB_AAP_1_23', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '23', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_BP/AAB_AAP_1_23.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_BP/AAB_AAP_1_30.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'NA', test_part: 'BP_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'BP_test', audio: 'AAB_AAP_1_30', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '30', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_BP/AAB_AAP_1_30.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_BP/AHB_AHP_3_0.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'NA', test_part: 'BP_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'BP_test', audio: 'AHB_AHP_3_0', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '0', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_BP/AHB_AHP_3_0.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_BP/AHB_AHP_3_3.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'NA', test_part: 'BP_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'BP_test', audio: 'AHB_AHP_3_3', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '3', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_BP/AHB_AHP_3_3.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_BP/AHB_AHP_3_5.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'NA', test_part: 'BP_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'BP_test', audio: 'AHB_AHP_3_5', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '5', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_BP/AHB_AHP_3_5.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_BP/AHB_AHP_3_7.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'NA', test_part: 'BP_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'BP_test', audio: 'AHB_AHP_3_7', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '7', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_BP/AHB_AHP_3_7.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_BP/AHB_AHP_3_9.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'NA', test_part: 'BP_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'BP_test', audio: 'AHB_AHP_3_9', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '9', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_BP/AHB_AHP_3_9.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_BP/AHB_AHP_3_10.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'NA', test_part: 'BP_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'BP_test', audio: 'AHB_AHP_3_10', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '10', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_BP/AHB_AHP_3_10.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_BP/AHB_AHP_3_11.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'NA', test_part: 'BP_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'BP_test', audio: 'AHB_AHP_3_11', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '11', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_BP/AHB_AHP_3_11.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_BP/AHB_AHP_3_13.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'NA', test_part: 'BP_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'BP_test', audio: 'AHB_AHP_3_13', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '13', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_BP/AHB_AHP_3_13.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_BP/AHB_AHP_3_17.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'NA', test_part: 'BP_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'BP_test', audio: 'AHB_AHP_3_17', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '17', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_BP/AHB_AHP_3_17.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_BP/AHB_AHP_3_23.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'NA', test_part: 'BP_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'BP_test', audio: 'AHB_AHP_3_23', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '23', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_BP/AHB_AHP_3_23.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_BP/AHB_AHP_3_30.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'NA', test_part: 'BP_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'BP_test', audio: 'AHB_AHP_3_30', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '30', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_BP/AHB_AHP_3_30.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_BP/IHB_IHP_5_0.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'NA', test_part: 'BP_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'BP_test', audio: 'IHB_IHP_5_0', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '7', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '0', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_BP/IHB_IHP_5_0.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_BP/IHB_IHP_5_2.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'NA', test_part: 'BP_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'BP_test', audio: 'IHB_IHP_5_2', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '7', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '2', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_BP/IHB_IHP_5_2.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_BP/IHB_IHP_5_4.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'NA', test_part: 'BP_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'BP_test', audio: 'IHB_IHP_5_4', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '7', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '4', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_BP/IHB_IHP_5_4.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_BP/IHB_IHP_5_5.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'NA', test_part: 'BP_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'BP_test', audio: 'IHB_IHP_5_5', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '7', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '5', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_BP/IHB_IHP_5_5.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_BP/IHB_IHP_5_6.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'NA', test_part: 'BP_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'BP_test', audio: 'IHB_IHP_5_6', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '7', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '6', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_BP/IHB_IHP_5_6.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_BP/IHB_IHP_5_7.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'NA', test_part: 'BP_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'BP_test', audio: 'IHB_IHP_5_7', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '7', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '7', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_BP/IHB_IHP_5_7.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_BP/IHB_IHP_5_9.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'NA', test_part: 'BP_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'BP_test', audio: 'IHB_IHP_5_9', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '7', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '9', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_BP/IHB_IHP_5_9.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_BP/IHB_IHP_5_11.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'NA', test_part: 'BP_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'BP_test', audio: 'IHB_IHP_5_11', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '7', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '11', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_BP/IHB_IHP_5_11.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_BP/IHB_IHP_5_15.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'NA', test_part: 'BP_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'BP_test', audio: 'IHB_IHP_5_15', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '7', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '15', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_BP/IHB_IHP_5_15.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_BP/IHB_IHP_5_22.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'NA', test_part: 'BP_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'BP_test', audio: 'IHB_IHP_5_22', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '7', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '22', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_BP/IHB_IHP_5_22.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_BP/IHB_IHP_5_30.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'NA', test_part: 'BP_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'BP_test', audio: 'IHB_IHP_5_30', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '7', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '30', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_BP/IHB_IHP_5_30.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_BP/UHB_UHP_5_0.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'NA', test_part: 'BP_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'BP_test', audio: 'UHB_UHP_5_0', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '7', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '0', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_BP/UHB_UHP_5_0.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_BP/UHB_UHP_5_2.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'NA', test_part: 'BP_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'BP_test', audio: 'UHB_UHP_5_2', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '7', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '2', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_BP/UHB_UHP_5_2.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_BP/UHB_UHP_5_4.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'NA', test_part: 'BP_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'BP_test', audio: 'UHB_UHP_5_4', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '7', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '4', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_BP/UHB_UHP_5_4.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_BP/UHB_UHP_5_5.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'NA', test_part: 'BP_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'BP_test', audio: 'UHB_UHP_5_5', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '7', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '5', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_BP/UHB_UHP_5_5.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_BP/UHB_UHP_5_6.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'NA', test_part: 'BP_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'BP_test', audio: 'UHB_UHP_5_6', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '7', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '6', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_BP/UHB_UHP_5_6.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_BP/UHB_UHP_5_7.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'NA', test_part: 'BP_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'BP_test', audio: 'UHB_UHP_5_7', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '7', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '7', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_BP/UHB_UHP_5_7.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_BP/UHB_UHP_5_9.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'NA', test_part: 'BP_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'BP_test', audio: 'UHB_UHP_5_9', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '7', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '9', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_BP/UHB_UHP_5_9.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_BP/UHB_UHP_5_11.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'NA', test_part: 'BP_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'BP_test', audio: 'UHB_UHP_5_11', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '7', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '11', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_BP/UHB_UHP_5_11.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_BP/UHB_UHP_5_15.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'NA', test_part: 'BP_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'BP_test', audio: 'UHB_UHP_5_15', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '7', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '15', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_BP/UHB_UHP_5_15.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_BP/UHB_UHP_5_21.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'NA', test_part: 'BP_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'BP_test', audio: 'UHB_UHP_5_21', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '7', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '21', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_BP/UHB_UHP_5_21.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_BP/UHB_UHP_5_30.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'NA', test_part: 'BP_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'BP_test', audio: 'UHB_UHP_5_30', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '7', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '30', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_BP/UHB_UHP_5_30.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_BP/AAB_AAP_1_0.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'NA', test_part: 'BP_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'BP_test', audio: 'AAB_AAP_1_0', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '0', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_BP/AAB_AAP_1_0.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_BP/AAB_AAP_1_3.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'NA', test_part: 'BP_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'BP_test', audio: 'AAB_AAP_1_3', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '3', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_BP/AAB_AAP_1_3.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_BP/AAB_AAP_1_5.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'NA', test_part: 'BP_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'BP_test', audio: 'AAB_AAP_1_5', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '5', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_BP/AAB_AAP_1_5.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_BP/AAB_AAP_1_7.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'NA', test_part: 'BP_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'BP_test', audio: 'AAB_AAP_1_7', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '7', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_BP/AAB_AAP_1_7.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_BP/AAB_AAP_1_9.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'NA', test_part: 'BP_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'BP_test', audio: 'AAB_AAP_1_9', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '9', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_BP/AAB_AAP_1_9.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_BP/AAB_AAP_1_10.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'NA', test_part: 'BP_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'BP_test', audio: 'AAB_AAP_1_10', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '10', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_BP/AAB_AAP_1_10.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_BP/AAB_AAP_1_11.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'NA', test_part: 'BP_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'BP_test', audio: 'AAB_AAP_1_11', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '11', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_BP/AAB_AAP_1_11.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_BP/AAB_AAP_1_13.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'NA', test_part: 'BP_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'BP_test', audio: 'AAB_AAP_1_13', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '13', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_BP/AAB_AAP_1_13.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_BP/AAB_AAP_1_17.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'NA', test_part: 'BP_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'BP_test', audio: 'AAB_AAP_1_17', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '17', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_BP/AAB_AAP_1_17.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_BP/AAB_AAP_1_23.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'NA', test_part: 'BP_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'BP_test', audio: 'AAB_AAP_1_23', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '23', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_BP/AAB_AAP_1_23.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_BP/AAB_AAP_1_30.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'NA', test_part: 'BP_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'BP_test', audio: 'AAB_AAP_1_30', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '30', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_BP/AAB_AAP_1_30.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_BP/AHB_AHP_3_0.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'NA', test_part: 'BP_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'BP_test', audio: 'AHB_AHP_3_0', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '0', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_BP/AHB_AHP_3_0.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_BP/AHB_AHP_3_3.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'NA', test_part: 'BP_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'BP_test', audio: 'AHB_AHP_3_3', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '3', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_BP/AHB_AHP_3_3.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_BP/AHB_AHP_3_5.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'NA', test_part: 'BP_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'BP_test', audio: 'AHB_AHP_3_5', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '5', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_BP/AHB_AHP_3_5.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_BP/AHB_AHP_3_7.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'NA', test_part: 'BP_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'BP_test', audio: 'AHB_AHP_3_7', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '7', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_BP/AHB_AHP_3_7.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_BP/AHB_AHP_3_9.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'NA', test_part: 'BP_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'BP_test', audio: 'AHB_AHP_3_9', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '9', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_BP/AHB_AHP_3_9.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_BP/AHB_AHP_3_10.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'NA', test_part: 'BP_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'BP_test', audio: 'AHB_AHP_3_10', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '10', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_BP/AHB_AHP_3_10.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_BP/AHB_AHP_3_11.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'NA', test_part: 'BP_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'BP_test', audio: 'AHB_AHP_3_11', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '11', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_BP/AHB_AHP_3_11.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_BP/AHB_AHP_3_13.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'NA', test_part: 'BP_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'BP_test', audio: 'AHB_AHP_3_13', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '13', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_BP/AHB_AHP_3_13.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_BP/AHB_AHP_3_17.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'NA', test_part: 'BP_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'BP_test', audio: 'AHB_AHP_3_17', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '17', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_BP/AHB_AHP_3_17.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_BP/AHB_AHP_3_23.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'NA', test_part: 'BP_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'BP_test', audio: 'AHB_AHP_3_23', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '23', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_BP/AHB_AHP_3_23.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_BP/AHB_AHP_3_30.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'NA', test_part: 'BP_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'BP_test', audio: 'AHB_AHP_3_30', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '30', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_BP/AHB_AHP_3_30.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_BP/IHB_IHP_5_0.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'NA', test_part: 'BP_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'BP_test', audio: 'IHB_IHP_5_0', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '7', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '0', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_BP/IHB_IHP_5_0.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_BP/IHB_IHP_5_2.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'NA', test_part: 'BP_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'BP_test', audio: 'IHB_IHP_5_2', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '7', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '2', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_BP/IHB_IHP_5_2.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_BP/IHB_IHP_5_4.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'NA', test_part: 'BP_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'BP_test', audio: 'IHB_IHP_5_4', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '7', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '4', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_BP/IHB_IHP_5_4.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_BP/IHB_IHP_5_5.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'NA', test_part: 'BP_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'BP_test', audio: 'IHB_IHP_5_5', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '7', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '5', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_BP/IHB_IHP_5_5.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_BP/IHB_IHP_5_6.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'NA', test_part: 'BP_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'BP_test', audio: 'IHB_IHP_5_6', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '7', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '6', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_BP/IHB_IHP_5_6.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_BP/IHB_IHP_5_7.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'NA', test_part: 'BP_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'BP_test', audio: 'IHB_IHP_5_7', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '7', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '7', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_BP/IHB_IHP_5_7.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_BP/IHB_IHP_5_9.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'NA', test_part: 'BP_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'BP_test', audio: 'IHB_IHP_5_9', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '7', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '9', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_BP/IHB_IHP_5_9.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_BP/IHB_IHP_5_11.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'NA', test_part: 'BP_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'BP_test', audio: 'IHB_IHP_5_11', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '7', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '11', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_BP/IHB_IHP_5_11.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_BP/IHB_IHP_5_15.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'NA', test_part: 'BP_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'BP_test', audio: 'IHB_IHP_5_15', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '7', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '15', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_BP/IHB_IHP_5_15.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_BP/IHB_IHP_5_22.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'NA', test_part: 'BP_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'BP_test', audio: 'IHB_IHP_5_22', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '7', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '22', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_BP/IHB_IHP_5_22.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_BP/IHB_IHP_5_30.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'NA', test_part: 'BP_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'BP_test', audio: 'IHB_IHP_5_30', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '7', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '30', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_BP/IHB_IHP_5_30.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_BP/UHB_UHP_5_0.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'NA', test_part: 'BP_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'BP_test', audio: 'UHB_UHP_5_0', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '7', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '0', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_BP/UHB_UHP_5_0.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_BP/UHB_UHP_5_2.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'NA', test_part: 'BP_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'BP_test', audio: 'UHB_UHP_5_2', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '7', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '2', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_BP/UHB_UHP_5_2.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_BP/UHB_UHP_5_4.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'NA', test_part: 'BP_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'BP_test', audio: 'UHB_UHP_5_4', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '7', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '4', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_BP/UHB_UHP_5_4.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_BP/UHB_UHP_5_5.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'NA', test_part: 'BP_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'BP_test', audio: 'UHB_UHP_5_5', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '7', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '5', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_BP/UHB_UHP_5_5.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_BP/UHB_UHP_5_6.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'NA', test_part: 'BP_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'BP_test', audio: 'UHB_UHP_5_6', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '7', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '6', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_BP/UHB_UHP_5_6.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_BP/UHB_UHP_5_7.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'NA', test_part: 'BP_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'BP_test', audio: 'UHB_UHP_5_7', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '7', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '7', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_BP/UHB_UHP_5_7.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_BP/UHB_UHP_5_9.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'NA', test_part: 'BP_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'BP_test', audio: 'UHB_UHP_5_9', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '7', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '9', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_BP/UHB_UHP_5_9.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_BP/UHB_UHP_5_11.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'NA', test_part: 'BP_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'BP_test', audio: 'UHB_UHP_5_11', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '7', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '11', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_BP/UHB_UHP_5_11.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_BP/UHB_UHP_5_15.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'NA', test_part: 'BP_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'BP_test', audio: 'UHB_UHP_5_15', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '7', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '15', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_BP/UHB_UHP_5_15.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_BP/UHB_UHP_5_21.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'NA', test_part: 'BP_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'BP_test', audio: 'UHB_UHP_5_21', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '7', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '21', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_BP/UHB_UHP_5_21.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_BP/UHB_UHP_5_30.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'NA', test_part: 'BP_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'BP_test', audio: 'UHB_UHP_5_30', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '7', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '30', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_BP/UHB_UHP_5_30.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_BP/AAB_AAP_1_0.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'NA', test_part: 'BP_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'BP_test', audio: 'AAB_AAP_1_0', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '0', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_BP/AAB_AAP_1_0.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_BP/AAB_AAP_1_3.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'NA', test_part: 'BP_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'BP_test', audio: 'AAB_AAP_1_3', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '3', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_BP/AAB_AAP_1_3.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_BP/AAB_AAP_1_5.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'NA', test_part: 'BP_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'BP_test', audio: 'AAB_AAP_1_5', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '5', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_BP/AAB_AAP_1_5.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_BP/AAB_AAP_1_7.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'NA', test_part: 'BP_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'BP_test', audio: 'AAB_AAP_1_7', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '7', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_BP/AAB_AAP_1_7.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_BP/AAB_AAP_1_9.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'NA', test_part: 'BP_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'BP_test', audio: 'AAB_AAP_1_9', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '9', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_BP/AAB_AAP_1_9.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_BP/AAB_AAP_1_10.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'NA', test_part: 'BP_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'BP_test', audio: 'AAB_AAP_1_10', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '10', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_BP/AAB_AAP_1_10.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_BP/AAB_AAP_1_11.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'NA', test_part: 'BP_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'BP_test', audio: 'AAB_AAP_1_11', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '11', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_BP/AAB_AAP_1_11.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_BP/AAB_AAP_1_13.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'NA', test_part: 'BP_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'BP_test', audio: 'AAB_AAP_1_13', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '13', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_BP/AAB_AAP_1_13.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_BP/AAB_AAP_1_17.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'NA', test_part: 'BP_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'BP_test', audio: 'AAB_AAP_1_17', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '17', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_BP/AAB_AAP_1_17.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_BP/AAB_AAP_1_23.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'NA', test_part: 'BP_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'BP_test', audio: 'AAB_AAP_1_23', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '23', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_BP/AAB_AAP_1_23.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_BP/AAB_AAP_1_30.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'NA', test_part: 'BP_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'BP_test', audio: 'AAB_AAP_1_30', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '30', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_BP/AAB_AAP_1_30.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_BP/AHB_AHP_3_0.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'NA', test_part: 'BP_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'BP_test', audio: 'AHB_AHP_3_0', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '0', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_BP/AHB_AHP_3_0.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_BP/AHB_AHP_3_3.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'NA', test_part: 'BP_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'BP_test', audio: 'AHB_AHP_3_3', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '3', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_BP/AHB_AHP_3_3.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_BP/AHB_AHP_3_5.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'NA', test_part: 'BP_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'BP_test', audio: 'AHB_AHP_3_5', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '5', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_BP/AHB_AHP_3_5.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_BP/AHB_AHP_3_7.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'NA', test_part: 'BP_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'BP_test', audio: 'AHB_AHP_3_7', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '7', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_BP/AHB_AHP_3_7.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_BP/AHB_AHP_3_9.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'NA', test_part: 'BP_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'BP_test', audio: 'AHB_AHP_3_9', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '9', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_BP/AHB_AHP_3_9.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_BP/AHB_AHP_3_10.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'NA', test_part: 'BP_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'BP_test', audio: 'AHB_AHP_3_10', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '10', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_BP/AHB_AHP_3_10.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_BP/AHB_AHP_3_11.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'NA', test_part: 'BP_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'BP_test', audio: 'AHB_AHP_3_11', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '11', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_BP/AHB_AHP_3_11.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_BP/AHB_AHP_3_13.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'NA', test_part: 'BP_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'BP_test', audio: 'AHB_AHP_3_13', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '13', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_BP/AHB_AHP_3_13.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_BP/AHB_AHP_3_17.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'NA', test_part: 'BP_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'BP_test', audio: 'AHB_AHP_3_17', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '17', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_BP/AHB_AHP_3_17.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_BP/AHB_AHP_3_23.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'NA', test_part: 'BP_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'BP_test', audio: 'AHB_AHP_3_23', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '23', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_BP/AHB_AHP_3_23.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_BP/AHB_AHP_3_30.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'NA', test_part: 'BP_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'BP_test', audio: 'AHB_AHP_3_30', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '30', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_BP/AHB_AHP_3_30.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_BP/IHB_IHP_5_0.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'NA', test_part: 'BP_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'BP_test', audio: 'IHB_IHP_5_0', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '7', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '0', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_BP/IHB_IHP_5_0.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_BP/IHB_IHP_5_2.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'NA', test_part: 'BP_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'BP_test', audio: 'IHB_IHP_5_2', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '7', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '2', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_BP/IHB_IHP_5_2.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_BP/IHB_IHP_5_4.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'NA', test_part: 'BP_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'BP_test', audio: 'IHB_IHP_5_4', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '7', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '4', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_BP/IHB_IHP_5_4.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_BP/IHB_IHP_5_5.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'NA', test_part: 'BP_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'BP_test', audio: 'IHB_IHP_5_5', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '7', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '5', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_BP/IHB_IHP_5_5.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_BP/IHB_IHP_5_6.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'NA', test_part: 'BP_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'BP_test', audio: 'IHB_IHP_5_6', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '7', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '6', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_BP/IHB_IHP_5_6.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_BP/IHB_IHP_5_7.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'NA', test_part: 'BP_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'BP_test', audio: 'IHB_IHP_5_7', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '7', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '7', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_BP/IHB_IHP_5_7.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_BP/IHB_IHP_5_9.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'NA', test_part: 'BP_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'BP_test', audio: 'IHB_IHP_5_9', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '7', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '9', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_BP/IHB_IHP_5_9.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_BP/IHB_IHP_5_11.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'NA', test_part: 'BP_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'BP_test', audio: 'IHB_IHP_5_11', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '7', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '11', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_BP/IHB_IHP_5_11.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_BP/IHB_IHP_5_15.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'NA', test_part: 'BP_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'BP_test', audio: 'IHB_IHP_5_15', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '7', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '15', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_BP/IHB_IHP_5_15.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_BP/IHB_IHP_5_22.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'NA', test_part: 'BP_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'BP_test', audio: 'IHB_IHP_5_22', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '7', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '22', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_BP/IHB_IHP_5_22.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_BP/IHB_IHP_5_30.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'NA', test_part: 'BP_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'BP_test', audio: 'IHB_IHP_5_30', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '7', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '30', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_BP/IHB_IHP_5_30.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_BP/UHB_UHP_5_0.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'NA', test_part: 'BP_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'BP_test', audio: 'UHB_UHP_5_0', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '7', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '0', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_BP/UHB_UHP_5_0.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_BP/UHB_UHP_5_2.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'NA', test_part: 'BP_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'BP_test', audio: 'UHB_UHP_5_2', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '7', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '2', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_BP/UHB_UHP_5_2.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_BP/UHB_UHP_5_4.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'NA', test_part: 'BP_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'BP_test', audio: 'UHB_UHP_5_4', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '7', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '4', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_BP/UHB_UHP_5_4.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_BP/UHB_UHP_5_5.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'NA', test_part: 'BP_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'BP_test', audio: 'UHB_UHP_5_5', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '7', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '5', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_BP/UHB_UHP_5_5.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_BP/UHB_UHP_5_6.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'NA', test_part: 'BP_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'BP_test', audio: 'UHB_UHP_5_6', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '7', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '6', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_BP/UHB_UHP_5_6.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_BP/UHB_UHP_5_7.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'NA', test_part: 'BP_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'BP_test', audio: 'UHB_UHP_5_7', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '7', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '7', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_BP/UHB_UHP_5_7.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_BP/UHB_UHP_5_9.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'NA', test_part: 'BP_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'BP_test', audio: 'UHB_UHP_5_9', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '7', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '9', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_BP/UHB_UHP_5_9.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_BP/UHB_UHP_5_11.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'NA', test_part: 'BP_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'BP_test', audio: 'UHB_UHP_5_11', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '7', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '11', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_BP/UHB_UHP_5_11.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_BP/UHB_UHP_5_15.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'NA', test_part: 'BP_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'BP_test', audio: 'UHB_UHP_5_15', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '7', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '15', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_BP/UHB_UHP_5_15.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_BP/UHB_UHP_5_21.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'NA', test_part: 'BP_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'BP_test', audio: 'UHB_UHP_5_21', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '7', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '21', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_BP/UHB_UHP_5_21.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_BP/UHB_UHP_5_30.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'NA', test_part: 'BP_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'BP_test', audio: 'UHB_UHP_5_30', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '7', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '30', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_BP/UHB_UHP_5_30.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_BP/AAB_AAP_1_0.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'NA', test_part: 'BP_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'BP_test', audio: 'AAB_AAP_1_0', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '0', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_BP/AAB_AAP_1_0.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_BP/AAB_AAP_1_3.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'NA', test_part: 'BP_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'BP_test', audio: 'AAB_AAP_1_3', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '3', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_BP/AAB_AAP_1_3.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_BP/AAB_AAP_1_5.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'NA', test_part: 'BP_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'BP_test', audio: 'AAB_AAP_1_5', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '5', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_BP/AAB_AAP_1_5.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_BP/AAB_AAP_1_7.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'NA', test_part: 'BP_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'BP_test', audio: 'AAB_AAP_1_7', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '7', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_BP/AAB_AAP_1_7.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_BP/AAB_AAP_1_9.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'NA', test_part: 'BP_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'BP_test', audio: 'AAB_AAP_1_9', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '9', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_BP/AAB_AAP_1_9.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_BP/AAB_AAP_1_10.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'NA', test_part: 'BP_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'BP_test', audio: 'AAB_AAP_1_10', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '10', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_BP/AAB_AAP_1_10.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_BP/AAB_AAP_1_11.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'NA', test_part: 'BP_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'BP_test', audio: 'AAB_AAP_1_11', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '11', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_BP/AAB_AAP_1_11.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_BP/AAB_AAP_1_13.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'NA', test_part: 'BP_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'BP_test', audio: 'AAB_AAP_1_13', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '13', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_BP/AAB_AAP_1_13.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_BP/AAB_AAP_1_17.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'NA', test_part: 'BP_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'BP_test', audio: 'AAB_AAP_1_17', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '17', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_BP/AAB_AAP_1_17.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_BP/AAB_AAP_1_23.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'NA', test_part: 'BP_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'BP_test', audio: 'AAB_AAP_1_23', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '23', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_BP/AAB_AAP_1_23.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_BP/AAB_AAP_1_30.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'NA', test_part: 'BP_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'BP_test', audio: 'AAB_AAP_1_30', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '30', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_BP/AAB_AAP_1_30.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_BP/AHB_AHP_3_0.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'NA', test_part: 'BP_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'BP_test', audio: 'AHB_AHP_3_0', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '0', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_BP/AHB_AHP_3_0.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_BP/AHB_AHP_3_3.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'NA', test_part: 'BP_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'BP_test', audio: 'AHB_AHP_3_3', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '3', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_BP/AHB_AHP_3_3.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_BP/AHB_AHP_3_5.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'NA', test_part: 'BP_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'BP_test', audio: 'AHB_AHP_3_5', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '5', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_BP/AHB_AHP_3_5.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_BP/AHB_AHP_3_7.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'NA', test_part: 'BP_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'BP_test', audio: 'AHB_AHP_3_7', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '7', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_BP/AHB_AHP_3_7.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_BP/AHB_AHP_3_9.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'NA', test_part: 'BP_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'BP_test', audio: 'AHB_AHP_3_9', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '9', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_BP/AHB_AHP_3_9.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_BP/AHB_AHP_3_10.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'NA', test_part: 'BP_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'BP_test', audio: 'AHB_AHP_3_10', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '10', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_BP/AHB_AHP_3_10.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_BP/AHB_AHP_3_11.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'NA', test_part: 'BP_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'BP_test', audio: 'AHB_AHP_3_11', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '11', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_BP/AHB_AHP_3_11.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_BP/AHB_AHP_3_13.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'NA', test_part: 'BP_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'BP_test', audio: 'AHB_AHP_3_13', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '13', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_BP/AHB_AHP_3_13.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_BP/AHB_AHP_3_17.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'NA', test_part: 'BP_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'BP_test', audio: 'AHB_AHP_3_17', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '17', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_BP/AHB_AHP_3_17.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_BP/AHB_AHP_3_23.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'NA', test_part: 'BP_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'BP_test', audio: 'AHB_AHP_3_23', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '23', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_BP/AHB_AHP_3_23.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_BP/AHB_AHP_3_30.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'NA', test_part: 'BP_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'BP_test', audio: 'AHB_AHP_3_30', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '30', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_BP/AHB_AHP_3_30.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_BP/IHB_IHP_5_0.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'NA', test_part: 'BP_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'BP_test', audio: 'IHB_IHP_5_0', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '7', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '0', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_BP/IHB_IHP_5_0.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_BP/IHB_IHP_5_2.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'NA', test_part: 'BP_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'BP_test', audio: 'IHB_IHP_5_2', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '7', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '2', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_BP/IHB_IHP_5_2.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_BP/IHB_IHP_5_4.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'NA', test_part: 'BP_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'BP_test', audio: 'IHB_IHP_5_4', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '7', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '4', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_BP/IHB_IHP_5_4.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_BP/IHB_IHP_5_5.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'NA', test_part: 'BP_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'BP_test', audio: 'IHB_IHP_5_5', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '7', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '5', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_BP/IHB_IHP_5_5.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_BP/IHB_IHP_5_6.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'NA', test_part: 'BP_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'BP_test', audio: 'IHB_IHP_5_6', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '7', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '6', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_BP/IHB_IHP_5_6.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_BP/IHB_IHP_5_7.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'NA', test_part: 'BP_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'BP_test', audio: 'IHB_IHP_5_7', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '7', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '7', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_BP/IHB_IHP_5_7.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_BP/IHB_IHP_5_9.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'NA', test_part: 'BP_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'BP_test', audio: 'IHB_IHP_5_9', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '7', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '9', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_BP/IHB_IHP_5_9.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_BP/IHB_IHP_5_11.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'NA', test_part: 'BP_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'BP_test', audio: 'IHB_IHP_5_11', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '7', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '11', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_BP/IHB_IHP_5_11.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_BP/IHB_IHP_5_15.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'NA', test_part: 'BP_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'BP_test', audio: 'IHB_IHP_5_15', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '7', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '15', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_BP/IHB_IHP_5_15.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_BP/IHB_IHP_5_22.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'NA', test_part: 'BP_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'BP_test', audio: 'IHB_IHP_5_22', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '7', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '22', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_BP/IHB_IHP_5_22.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_BP/IHB_IHP_5_30.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'NA', test_part: 'BP_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'BP_test', audio: 'IHB_IHP_5_30', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '7', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '30', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_BP/IHB_IHP_5_30.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_BP/UHB_UHP_5_0.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'NA', test_part: 'BP_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'BP_test', audio: 'UHB_UHP_5_0', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '7', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '0', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_BP/UHB_UHP_5_0.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_BP/UHB_UHP_5_2.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'NA', test_part: 'BP_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'BP_test', audio: 'UHB_UHP_5_2', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '7', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '2', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_BP/UHB_UHP_5_2.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_BP/UHB_UHP_5_4.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'NA', test_part: 'BP_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'BP_test', audio: 'UHB_UHP_5_4', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '7', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '4', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_BP/UHB_UHP_5_4.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_BP/UHB_UHP_5_5.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'NA', test_part: 'BP_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'BP_test', audio: 'UHB_UHP_5_5', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '7', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '5', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_BP/UHB_UHP_5_5.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_BP/UHB_UHP_5_6.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'NA', test_part: 'BP_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'BP_test', audio: 'UHB_UHP_5_6', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '7', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '6', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_BP/UHB_UHP_5_6.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_BP/UHB_UHP_5_7.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'NA', test_part: 'BP_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'BP_test', audio: 'UHB_UHP_5_7', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '7', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '7', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_BP/UHB_UHP_5_7.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_BP/UHB_UHP_5_9.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'NA', test_part: 'BP_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'BP_test', audio: 'UHB_UHP_5_9', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '7', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '9', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_BP/UHB_UHP_5_9.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_BP/UHB_UHP_5_11.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'NA', test_part: 'BP_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'BP_test', audio: 'UHB_UHP_5_11', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '7', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '11', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_BP/UHB_UHP_5_11.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_BP/UHB_UHP_5_15.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'NA', test_part: 'BP_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'BP_test', audio: 'UHB_UHP_5_15', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '7', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '15', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_BP/UHB_UHP_5_15.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_BP/UHB_UHP_5_21.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'NA', test_part: 'BP_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'BP_test', audio: 'UHB_UHP_5_21', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '7', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '21', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_BP/UHB_UHP_5_21.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_BP/UHB_UHP_5_30.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'NA', test_part: 'BP_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'BP_test', audio: 'UHB_UHP_5_30', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '7', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '30', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_BP/UHB_UHP_5_30.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_BP/AAB_AAP_1_0.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'NA', test_part: 'BP_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'BP_test', audio: 'AAB_AAP_1_0', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '0', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_BP/AAB_AAP_1_0.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_BP/AAB_AAP_1_3.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'NA', test_part: 'BP_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'BP_test', audio: 'AAB_AAP_1_3', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '3', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_BP/AAB_AAP_1_3.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_BP/AAB_AAP_1_5.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'NA', test_part: 'BP_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'BP_test', audio: 'AAB_AAP_1_5', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '5', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_BP/AAB_AAP_1_5.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_BP/AAB_AAP_1_7.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'NA', test_part: 'BP_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'BP_test', audio: 'AAB_AAP_1_7', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '7', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_BP/AAB_AAP_1_7.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_BP/AAB_AAP_1_9.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'NA', test_part: 'BP_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'BP_test', audio: 'AAB_AAP_1_9', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '9', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_BP/AAB_AAP_1_9.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_BP/AAB_AAP_1_10.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'NA', test_part: 'BP_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'BP_test', audio: 'AAB_AAP_1_10', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '10', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_BP/AAB_AAP_1_10.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_BP/AAB_AAP_1_11.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'NA', test_part: 'BP_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'BP_test', audio: 'AAB_AAP_1_11', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '11', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_BP/AAB_AAP_1_11.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_BP/AAB_AAP_1_13.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'NA', test_part: 'BP_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'BP_test', audio: 'AAB_AAP_1_13', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '13', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_BP/AAB_AAP_1_13.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_BP/AAB_AAP_1_17.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'NA', test_part: 'BP_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'BP_test', audio: 'AAB_AAP_1_17', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '17', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_BP/AAB_AAP_1_17.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_BP/AAB_AAP_1_23.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'NA', test_part: 'BP_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'BP_test', audio: 'AAB_AAP_1_23', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '23', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_BP/AAB_AAP_1_23.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_BP/AAB_AAP_1_30.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'NA', test_part: 'BP_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'BP_test', audio: 'AAB_AAP_1_30', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '30', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_BP/AAB_AAP_1_30.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_BP/AHB_AHP_3_0.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'NA', test_part: 'BP_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'BP_test', audio: 'AHB_AHP_3_0', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '0', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_BP/AHB_AHP_3_0.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_BP/AHB_AHP_3_3.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'NA', test_part: 'BP_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'BP_test', audio: 'AHB_AHP_3_3', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '3', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_BP/AHB_AHP_3_3.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_BP/AHB_AHP_3_5.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'NA', test_part: 'BP_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'BP_test', audio: 'AHB_AHP_3_5', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '5', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_BP/AHB_AHP_3_5.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_BP/AHB_AHP_3_7.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'NA', test_part: 'BP_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'BP_test', audio: 'AHB_AHP_3_7', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '7', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_BP/AHB_AHP_3_7.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_BP/AHB_AHP_3_9.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'NA', test_part: 'BP_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'BP_test', audio: 'AHB_AHP_3_9', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '9', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_BP/AHB_AHP_3_9.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_BP/AHB_AHP_3_10.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'NA', test_part: 'BP_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'BP_test', audio: 'AHB_AHP_3_10', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '10', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_BP/AHB_AHP_3_10.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_BP/AHB_AHP_3_11.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'NA', test_part: 'BP_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'BP_test', audio: 'AHB_AHP_3_11', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '11', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_BP/AHB_AHP_3_11.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_BP/AHB_AHP_3_13.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'NA', test_part: 'BP_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'BP_test', audio: 'AHB_AHP_3_13', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '13', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_BP/AHB_AHP_3_13.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_BP/AHB_AHP_3_17.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'NA', test_part: 'BP_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'BP_test', audio: 'AHB_AHP_3_17', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '17', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_BP/AHB_AHP_3_17.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_BP/AHB_AHP_3_23.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'NA', test_part: 'BP_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'BP_test', audio: 'AHB_AHP_3_23', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '23', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_BP/AHB_AHP_3_23.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_BP/AHB_AHP_3_30.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'NA', test_part: 'BP_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'BP_test', audio: 'AHB_AHP_3_30', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '30', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_BP/AHB_AHP_3_30.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_BP/IHB_IHP_5_0.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'NA', test_part: 'BP_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'BP_test', audio: 'IHB_IHP_5_0', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '7', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '0', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_BP/IHB_IHP_5_0.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_BP/IHB_IHP_5_2.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'NA', test_part: 'BP_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'BP_test', audio: 'IHB_IHP_5_2', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '7', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '2', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_BP/IHB_IHP_5_2.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_BP/IHB_IHP_5_4.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'NA', test_part: 'BP_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'BP_test', audio: 'IHB_IHP_5_4', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '7', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '4', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_BP/IHB_IHP_5_4.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_BP/IHB_IHP_5_5.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'NA', test_part: 'BP_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'BP_test', audio: 'IHB_IHP_5_5', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '7', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '5', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_BP/IHB_IHP_5_5.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_BP/IHB_IHP_5_6.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'NA', test_part: 'BP_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'BP_test', audio: 'IHB_IHP_5_6', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '7', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '6', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_BP/IHB_IHP_5_6.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_BP/IHB_IHP_5_7.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'NA', test_part: 'BP_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'BP_test', audio: 'IHB_IHP_5_7', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '7', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '7', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_BP/IHB_IHP_5_7.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_BP/IHB_IHP_5_9.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'NA', test_part: 'BP_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'BP_test', audio: 'IHB_IHP_5_9', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '7', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '9', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_BP/IHB_IHP_5_9.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_BP/IHB_IHP_5_11.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'NA', test_part: 'BP_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'BP_test', audio: 'IHB_IHP_5_11', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '7', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '11', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_BP/IHB_IHP_5_11.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_BP/IHB_IHP_5_15.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'NA', test_part: 'BP_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'BP_test', audio: 'IHB_IHP_5_15', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '7', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '15', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_BP/IHB_IHP_5_15.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_BP/IHB_IHP_5_22.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'NA', test_part: 'BP_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'BP_test', audio: 'IHB_IHP_5_22', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '7', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '22', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_BP/IHB_IHP_5_22.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_BP/IHB_IHP_5_30.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'NA', test_part: 'BP_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'BP_test', audio: 'IHB_IHP_5_30', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '7', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '30', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_BP/IHB_IHP_5_30.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_BP/UHB_UHP_5_0.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'NA', test_part: 'BP_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'BP_test', audio: 'UHB_UHP_5_0', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '7', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '0', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_BP/UHB_UHP_5_0.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_BP/UHB_UHP_5_2.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'NA', test_part: 'BP_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'BP_test', audio: 'UHB_UHP_5_2', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '7', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '2', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_BP/UHB_UHP_5_2.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_BP/UHB_UHP_5_4.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'NA', test_part: 'BP_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'BP_test', audio: 'UHB_UHP_5_4', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '7', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '4', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_BP/UHB_UHP_5_4.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_BP/UHB_UHP_5_5.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'NA', test_part: 'BP_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'BP_test', audio: 'UHB_UHP_5_5', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '7', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '5', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_BP/UHB_UHP_5_5.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_BP/UHB_UHP_5_6.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'NA', test_part: 'BP_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'BP_test', audio: 'UHB_UHP_5_6', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '7', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '6', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_BP/UHB_UHP_5_6.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_BP/UHB_UHP_5_7.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'NA', test_part: 'BP_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'BP_test', audio: 'UHB_UHP_5_7', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '7', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '7', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_BP/UHB_UHP_5_7.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_BP/UHB_UHP_5_9.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'NA', test_part: 'BP_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'BP_test', audio: 'UHB_UHP_5_9', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '7', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '9', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_BP/UHB_UHP_5_9.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_BP/UHB_UHP_5_11.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'NA', test_part: 'BP_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'BP_test', audio: 'UHB_UHP_5_11', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '7', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '11', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_BP/UHB_UHP_5_11.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_BP/UHB_UHP_5_15.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'NA', test_part: 'BP_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'BP_test', audio: 'UHB_UHP_5_15', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '7', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '15', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_BP/UHB_UHP_5_15.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_BP/UHB_UHP_5_21.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'NA', test_part: 'BP_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'BP_test', audio: 'UHB_UHP_5_21', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '7', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '21', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_BP/UHB_UHP_5_21.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_BP/UHB_UHP_5_30.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'NA', test_part: 'BP_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'BP_test', audio: 'UHB_UHP_5_30', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '7', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '30', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_BP/UHB_UHP_5_30.wav' }}]